(The final director's ultimate power)
(Who will you send to the Last Stage?)
(The bottom choreography selection)
(More than 2 votes will disqualify the director candidate.)
(The bottom choreography selection will eliminate candidates.)
(That's eliminating those who did bad.)
(I'm getting a bad feeling about this.)
(This is the fun part.)
(I'm not choosing them.)
(Even the good ones could be eliminated.)
(The strategic battle begins.)
(I don't have a big role in that choreography.)
(Something that wouldn't suit me...)
(10 choreographers' intense strategic battle)
(What remains now is...)
(to decide the choreographer...)
(for the Last Stage.)
(Revealing 3 worst director candidates for the Last Stage)
(The choreographer who will end up in the Last Stage is...)
(Renan?)
(Kasper?)
(I didn't think I'd end up in the Last Stage.)
(But I think I can make it.)
(I made too many mistakes.)
(I was too anxious.)
(I couldn't believe it was really happening.)
(The Title Sequence Film Mission shoot)
(Renan's going too fast.)
(She's off beat.)
(Going off beat is...)
(crucial to a dancer.)
(Who will be the first worst choreographer...)
(to end up in the Last Stage?)
(Who will be the 3 choreographer in the Last Stage?)
(Street World Fighter: Directors' War)
(The second mission...)
(is finally revealed.)
(The first scene that starts the show)
(The Title Sequence Film Mission took place last week.)
(Title Sequence Film Mission)
(It represents the show.)
(1 minute)
(9 dancers)
(And only 1 director)
(The director will be given the judge's power...)
(to decide the elimination candidates.)
(That's the ultimate power.)
(Their lives depend on the director battle.)
(I must win.)
(Director, choreographer, dancer)
(I have to become a director, obviously.)
(After this mission, )
(2 choreographers...)
(will be eliminated.)
(Two?)
(Already?)
(I'm suddenly feeling dizzy.)
(Concept and film draft presentation)
(Starting with BABYZOO, )
(10 choreographers presented their concept and drafts.)
(BABYZOO's draft video)
(Renan's draft video)
(Can you call yourselves directors with those drafts?)
(Simeez's draft video)
(Kasper's draft video)
(Displeased)
(Reckless criticisms toward each other)
(JEONG MIN JUN's draft video)
(BADA's draft video)
(Hash's draft video)
(NaiN's draft video)
(INGYOO's draft video)
(It was just a series of individual scenes.)
(Lastly, Back Koo Young's draft video)
(The one I'm worried about the most)
(I'm looking forward to watching his the most.)
(He has the biggest experience.)
(If I fail to show what I've got as a choreographer, )
(it's a failure.)
(Easy, simple, )
(and catchy)
(Which choreographer's name will be on the final director credit board?)
(Title Sequence Film Mission)
(Choreography draft credit board)
What? That's funny.
- What's that? - Gosh.
That's me.
(BABYZOO)
- I thought that was BABYZOO. - Isn't that BABYZOO?
It was something that I like.
(INGYOO)
(NaiN)
I'd be good at it.
I like that.
Is that Lia?
(INGYOO)
(I can't believe it.)
He knew what I needed.
He has a good understanding of us.
(Simeez)
Oh, Seo In.
I can never keep up with Gwacheon Honey Watermelon.
(Back Koo Young)
You're so handsome.
He made good use of himself.
In a way, it's a performance for himself.
The roles weren't distributed equally.
It felt like a film only for him.
(Back Koo Young)
(NaiN)
He gave me many important parts.
I was happy.
(BADA, Simeez, Back Koo Young, BABYZOO, Kasper)
(Cool!)
Just as expected.
I think Koo Young's was the best.
It was the standard example of a title video.
It was very simple.
So it got me thinking,
"Why didn't I think like that?"
You removed all the unnecessary parts.
Personally, I liked it very much because of that.
I think it was a good idea to focus on that.
I liked how you showed everyone...
without focusing too much on dancing.
Especially the verse.
I liked the smooth transition.
That's Koo Young's directing.
Just when I began to think the verse was pointless...
because he had to meet the concept,
he used that sequence...
to present our charms one by one.
He did a good job of connecting them.
I could see...
how much you studied us.
But in the end,
you took the lead role.
Koo Young appeared more often...
than other people.
Of course, that's up to the director,
but you took too many parts.
I still gave everyone a part.
I already wrote...
that it moves fast.
That shouldn't be an issue.
I only get one scene.
It's too short. "The light" is all I get.
(INGYOO only appears briefly during the transition.)
(BADA gets one scene in the intro.)
(Hash gets one scene during the verse.)
It felt like a film only for him.
That was exactly what I intended.
In the end, it's a TV show.
I have to be loved...
by as many people as I can.
I must get it.
Because I need to win.
(The concept and the video presentation ends.)
(Which choreographer will become a director?)
How can we exclude one?
(More than 2 votes will disqualify the director candidate.)
It was shocking.
By voting?
Then...
It's a matter of who gets eliminated from the evaluation.
I'm getting a bad feeling about this.
It'd be awful to receive two votes.
Now?
Oh, my gosh.
I knew it'd be tough.
- We have to write who did bad. - And why it was bad.
This is what makes it fun.
(Worried)
This is going to be tough.
I'm traumatized by the internal evaluation.
(1-on-1 Signature 400 Mission)
(Lost the choreography evaluation)
(Lost the interim check)
I never won the internal evaluation before.
My hair's going to fall out.
It's going to be tough.
We're going to appear in the title sequence film.
That's going to be crucial.
We're going to be the ones dancing.
I hope it's not something so obvious.
I don't want to be in any ordinary dance video.
There was no content.
I don't remember anything about it. That's also a problem.
I'm not going to pick them.
It was kind of maniac.
I'm not going to stand out in that video.
There are a few people who are completely off.
First, it can never be...
That's not my type.
That's the most important reason.
(Through the internal evaluation, )
(anyone with more than 2 votes will become the weakest dancer.)
(They'll be removed from the director candidate immediately.)
(Whose draft did Renan choose as the weakest?)
The one to be removed from the director candidate is...
I have to pick the worst, not someone I want to work with.
Can you play BABYZOO's again?
(Renan is contemplating.)
MIN JUN was a bit...
Kasper also...
It's a matter of whether I want to do it or not.
Because it's something I have to do.
She wouldn't pick me.
I hoped not to hear my name.
It wouldn't be me.
The one to be removed from the director candidate is...
Kasper.
(Bitter)
What? Me again?
But why? Why me?
It made me anxious.
(Whose draft did JEONG MIN JUN pick as the weakest?)
MIN JUN? I'm in trouble.
(It's a film, )
(but moving forward and backward...)
(using the wide angle?)
(I don't really like that.)
(It's just the typical K-pop draft...)
(that K-pop videos demand.)
MIN JUN is very competitive.
How can he be the youngest?
I got the feeling that other people didn't really like him.
This is not good.
I shouldn't have said what I said earlier.
(It didn't seem very persuasive.)
(Your description was lengthy, )
(but I didn't see any connection.)
(I don't think you made...)
(each choreographer's charm stand out.)
I had this in mind.
"If I say this,"
"he'd say this about me."
Yet I said it because someone had to tell him.
The one to be removed from the director candidate is...
I'm worried.
What if I lose again?
I'm getting the chills.
The one to be removed from the director candidate is...
Kasper.
For real?
Every time I do something, I'm out.
I was glad it wasn't me.
This is really scary.
This place is cruel.
I thought about whether...
it depicts what the narrator wants to say clearly.
And it was more of a dance video.
I thought it was rather a standard example of a dance video.
I kind of thought you should've focused more on telling a story.
I think the film was rather too light.
What about yours?
It was nothing new.
The choreography for each dancer was a shame.
But he probably thinks his was innovative.
It was ridiculous.
His concept wasn't clear.
I personally think it was too ordinary.
It didn't make sense.
For ridiculous reasons,
I'm the first to be eliminated.
(Absurd)
(Eliminated)
The one to be removed from the director candidate is...
I kept praying.
I don't know.
I have a feeling he might pick me.
But I won't regret making comments on him.
It was crazy intense.
Renan.
(1 vote)
Is this really happening?
I was so relieved.
I knew other people were going to pick MIN JUN anyway.
She didn't make good use of the choreographers.
The female dancers had the lead roles.
It was more of Renan's choreography video...
rather than introducing everyone.
This is nonsense.
I don't know.
But everyone's opinion is different.
People have similar tastes.
I pick Renan's film.
I couldn't believe it was really happening.
(3 votes)
It really upset me.
It wasn't appealing at all.
I didn't see any point of trying something new.
Five female directors' twerking...
totally cost her the points.
She's not planning to customize the directors.
I chose her because I don't think she has what it takes...
to lead all ten of us.
I really wanted to cry.
(Selection complete, selection complete, eliminated)
(Eliminated, selection complete)
These people are brutal.
It must feel like falling into a fire pit.
I knew MIN JUN would be eliminated.
I have a feeling it could be me.
I'm kind of anxious.
It'll be INGYOO for sure.
No one would choose me.
It has to be Koo Young and BADA.
Come on. I doubt it.
Gosh, I'm so nervous.
(Simeez picks the weakest next.)
Honestly, I'm worried.
I kind of went after Simeez.
She might pick me.
The one I chose to remove from the director candidate is...
This is getting really important.
BADA.
(Choosing BADA as the weakest)
What? Why?
It was kind of unexpected.
Perhaps it could've been her strategy.
I added everything, including props and the concept.
I didn't expect to get any votes at all.
(4 people still haven't chosen the weakest draft yet.)
Just one vote. I wasn't sure. I was anxious.
It wouldn't be me. But maybe?
I can't even guess.
I was afraid. I was worried so much.
The one to be removed from the director candidate is...
I was so nervous. I just hoped it wouldn't be me.
Please don't pick me.
JEONG MIN JUN.
I had a lot on my mind.
I saw that coming.
MIN JUN had all the reasons to be picked.
(A relieved sigh)
(Laughing)
His description was pretty good.
(The choreographers enter the building.)
(They implement their missions.)
(They're after the crown.)
(That sounds fun.)
(It'll be fun to film it.)
But that didn't appear...
in the film.
I'd do a way better job...
of doing MIN JUN's work.
I couldn't find any new performance...
in this mission video.
He made it seem like he prepared a lot.
But what he said didn't match what he showed us.
I thought he put a lot of thoughts into it because it was so lengthy.
But it didn't show that he put any thought into it.
I didn't think it was that bad.
I mean, someone would definitely vote for me.
But I hope no more than one.
(Who did Hash pick for the weakest draft?)
I was anxious.
She wouldn't pick me.
The one to be removed from the director candidate is...
MIN JUN.
JEONG MIN JUN.
(Screaming)
(JEONG MIN JUN is eliminated from the director candidate.)
It's upsetting, annoying, and embarrassing.
I picked the one...
I least wanted to dance to.
That was harsh.
She did a lot of MIN JUN's choreography last week.
Right.
It was shocking.
The film I don't want to dance to.
It wasn't that touching.
Without that concept,
this film might become childish.
He still seems to have narrow sight.
I want to present...
how good we can dance and how good we can choreograph.
It'll be the first video the public will see.
It felt like it missed a lot. That's why I chose it.
I'm glad it's not me.
That was discouraging.
The arrows hit me right here.
Someone had to tell him.
I hope his passion leads him to a good path.
But I got the feeling that it might isolate him.
(The weakest choreography has been chosen.)
(JEONG MIN JUN, Renan, and Kasper are eliminated...)
(from the director candidates.)
The two director candidates.
They have the power over the Last Stage.
Who are they going to eliminate first?
It has to be me. I hope it's me.
It's the most powerful authority.
I have to pick what I want to do.
I should come up with a strategy carefully.
I have to worry about who'd prevent me from the Last Stage.
I think I'm the best main director candidate.
It's time for my lethal move.
I must win no matter what.
I want to be the face of this show.
(Who will become the 2 director candidates?)
The first eliminated candidate Kasper's...
choice of the director candidate is...
I'm eliminated from the candidate.
(I'm first to be eliminated.)
Now that this happened,
I might as well choose something where I appear the most...
I like this section and this choreography.
Which part did I get?
Now, I'm a dancer.
I must survive.
As a dancer, it was very clear.
Because I just need to pull off my part.
(Who did the 2 people eliminated from the candidate choose?)
I choose Back Koo Young and...
BABYZOO.
(1 vote each)
I choose INGYOO and Hash.
I was attracted to those...
who tried something new.
BABYZOO's choreography...
constitutes a structure...
that shows the way I dance.
I liked his choreography.
I knew that'd show who I am.
For Koo Young,
there weren't unnecessary movements.
He made it clear.
That was the only one that could show who I am.
The only person I can trust aside from me is...
Koo Young.
Kasper knew by instinct.
That I'd totally pull it off.
He knows me so well.
(Current status of the director candidate vote)
(1 vote each)
The choreographers I choose for the director candidate are...
Back Koo Young and Simeez.
(2 votes, 1 vote)
I thought about someone who could...
direct ten choreographers.
Persuasiveness and stability from experience.
That doesn't necessarily mean age and long years of experience.
But a number of works and the range.
Someone who's capable of iconic directing even for a short film.
Their level of directing is on another level.
(1 vote each)
(2 votes, 1 vote)
The choreographers I choose for the director candidate are...
Hash and Simeez.
(2 votes each)
Oh, good.
I thought it should be something different.
I wanted it to be completely different.
All ten of us must stand out in the end.
I found Hash's very appealing.
Whereas Simeez's makes all ten of us stand out.
It'll be an intriguing and new way of directing.
(1 vote, 1 vote, 2 votes)
(2 votes each)
At this rate, I won this.
This is bad.
This is going to be a tough fight.
The choreographers I choose for the director candidate are...
A new choreography that I want to dance to.
NaiN and INGYOO.
(1 vote, 2 votes)
INGYOO? But why?
Why? Why is that?
At first, I wasn't thinking about INGYOO.
He created...
a solo part for me.
I knew that'd persuade her.
It's simple, yet smart and good.
(2 votes, 1 vote, 2 votes)
(1 vote, 2 votes, 2 votes)
(0 votes)
This is shocking.
I thought I was at risk.
I thought I had a chance.
(Their fate depends on the remaining 5 choreographers' choices.)
The choreographers I choose for the director candidate are...
Gosh, this is tense.
This will represent the show.
The Title Sequence Film Mission...
has a purpose.
The answer is clear.
The choreographers I choose for the director candidate are...
Come on. I can't let that happen.
Please say my name.
I want to be a director.
BADA and NaiN.
(2 votes, 1 vote)
Personally, I was relieved to hear my name.
That gave me the chills. "Is that going to happen again?"
Back Koo Young and...
Please say my name.
BADA. Please let it be my name.
Back Koo Young and BADA.
(3 votes, 2 votes)
Nothing goes as I expect.
This is never easy.
When I saw the choreography,
it looked fun,
and it was something I'm good at.
I think it's well made.
If we assume the object in the film is a trophy,
it totally makes sense, and I like the choreography.
I'm expecting it to be a solid film.
There's no need to mention it. BADA is amazing.
(2 votes each)
I might have a chance.
To be honest, I was very anxious.
(2 votes, 1 vote, 2 votes)
(2. votes, 3 votes, 2 votes, 2 votes)
(Only 3 people left to vote)
Things aren't going so easy today.
I never know.
This is unpredictable.
Gosh, I can't tell.
(Next, BADA's vote)
The choreographers I choose...
for the director candidate are...
NaiN and INGYOO.
(3 votes each)
Renan wouldn't have picked me.
I thought it was over.
NaiN showed exactly what she wanted to show.
I think it was best structured.
("Game of Thrones")
(It's well made.)
(I love it.)
(It's fun to watch.)
(That was really neat.)
It was easy to understand.
Who had the safest, the coolest,
and the most stable choreography to present my charms?
I think that was NaiN.
In terms of the balance,
I thought I was in favor.
I'm getting anxious.
Many of us tied.
It made me nervous.
This is so tough.
I couldn't even guess. I was anxious.
(Only Simeez and Renan left to choose)
I was so nervous. My heart was pounding so fast.
I'm the only one who deserves to be a director.
It's been so long since I had someone else direct me.
If I can't be a director, I'm going home.
I think I'm the most suitable to be the main director.
I deserve the director title.
The choreographers I choose for the director candidate are...
I'm not thinking about anything other than first place.
I have to make the Director Credit.
I'm taking the Director Credit.
- I'll take it. - It's mine.
He'll have to give up.
Back Koo Young and NaiN.
(4 votes each)
NaiN and Back Koo Young.
(2 director candidates are NaiN and Back Koo Young.)
(Congratulations)
Thank you.
Way to go!
I was really happy.
They might have picked me...
based on my experience.
There is definitely something I don't have in terms of experience.
But I hope it becomes a chance...
for me to prove myself as a director.
I wanted to pick someone who worked hard.
NaiN and Koo Young's drafts had the highest quality.
It's something anyone will like.
It's my first time getting directed by NaiN.
I'm looking forward to it.
Because it's my first time seeing her directing.
The experience makes a huge difference.
It's a battle between the first generation and the rookie.
It's going to be very fun.
(Title Sequence Film Mission final director candidates)
Gosh.
(After selecting 2 director candidates)
(Kasper watches NaiN's draft again.)
(Groaning)
I don't think I can do it.
Nod
That first dimensional expression is quite embarrassing.
I was anxious.
I'm participating as a dancer, not a director.
It was a shame.
I'm kind of worried about Koo Young's video.
I have a feeling he won't make good use of me.
It'd feel like filming a K-pop artist music video.
So I wanted to void both NaiN and Koo Young's.
I'm afraid NaiN won't be able to...
bring out the best in me.
I would've done well as a director.
Now that I'm not a director,
I need to prepare myself for the worst.
The red alarm went off in my head.
Directing all these dancers?
(Exclaiming)
I'm so jealous.
I loved it.
Honestly, I tried so hard not to smile.
I love my job even more now.
I wish I could be the final director.
It's got to be me.
It has to be me,
so I can make a great film.
(NaiN and Back Koo Young's Directors' Rooms.)
For this part...
Maybe a drone...
In terms of clothes...
To express them...
There are escalators...
I'll send it to you before today.
They're having a meeting right away?
(In a meeting)
They look like they're having a meeting with the production team.
I was jealous. I wish I was a director.
It'd be so much fun.
I was jealous.
I was really jealous.
I'm jealous.
But the candidates have already been chosen.
The final director has...
the power to send us to the Last Stage.
Now that I'm not a director,
I have to come up with a strategy
to avoid going to the Last Stage.
I'd better try so hard...
that the final director would feel awful to pick me.
(Renan is already practicing the choreography.)
I practiced the choreography in advance.
(BADA visits NaiN's room.)
- NaiN. - Yes.
- Are you thirsty? - Really?
I'm going to win the director candidates' favor.
I look forward to working with you.
I look forward to working with you too.
Is she on it already?
Buttering up like this...
I think that is...
Let me know if you need my help.
Cunning.
Be my keychain man again.
(Smiling)
No way.
Kasper's working so hard to avoid the Last Stage.
(BADA also delivers a drink to Back Koo Young.)
- Nice? Yes. - That was my strategy.
I look forward to working with you.
I'll keep you in center for three more seconds.
(Nice!)
(I'm watching you.)
If there's anything you like in my draft,
feel free to use it.
- It's all yours. - You can use mine too.
- Anything you want. - Your right-hand and left-hand.
We're both long.
- Exactly. - We're the tallest here.
Can you guys...
make a chair with your arms?
(The taste of the power)
Look at them. They're going crazy.
It's a matter of being in power.
We're also evaluating the director candidates.
(The game changer of the final director determination)
(Vote by 8 choreographers)
I'll have to see their direction.
How well they express me.
How exciting and good my part is.
How well they bring out the best in everyone.
We selected them based on the draft video.
But in the end, it's all about their direction.
I'm confident.
I have a good understanding of this mission,
and I know what I'm doing from all those years of experience.
They have to direct...
those who make a living by directing.
It'll never be easy...
for the youngest to control us.
I'm expecting NaiN's to be sensational.
I want NaiN to start a sensation...
among the exceptionally talented people.
Then let's do stretching and get started.
- Okay. - All right.
Now that the Director...
has been officially decided,
I'll fall right into line.
If you need any help, please feel free to let me know.
It's starting now.
I think everyone was trying to read the room.
After all, they hold the power to send someone...
to the Last Stage.
Since Hash's part needs a chair...
A chair? I'll grab a chair.
- Where? - I'll get it.
Is this all right?
- Deduct points for this. - Points deducted.
Director, here you go.
(Satisfied)
I really wanted to run over...
and dash for it too.
Excuse me, could someone give me a hand with this just once?
Let me help you out!
Wait, Director.
- Wait a second. - Wait, Director.
Everyone was just so fast.
- This is so funny. - We keep doing this.
A man should lift this.
The other choreographers...
were trying so hard to treat me well and help out.
I was so grateful.
But INGYOO...
I think you just need...
to push this hand out like this.
- Okay. - Okay.
Director, INGYOO is just doing whatever he wants.
Deduct points from him.
I just want to show there are other options.
- Okay. - I can do this right away.
This is crazy.
INGYOO, you're on fire.
Who would ever want to go to the Last Stage?
Nice.
It looks great.
(This time, he's cheering with his entire body.)
Nice!
What is with him?
NaiN, a candidate for elimination is right here.
What are you talking about?
I'm going all out so she will look favorably on me.
Why does he keep doing that?
This is exactly why people go crazy over power.
This is why.
The kids were just so cute.
(Sliding in)
(Seizing the perfect chance to butter him up)
Genius.
This is amazing.
It feels good anyway.
I'm thankful, after all.
But then this thought crossed my mind. "Wait."
"I think they're misunderstanding something."
I need a majority vote,
including the public evaluation,
to become the Director.
Then what do I need to do to appeal...
to the choreographers instead?
(Back Koo's flattery begins.)
- Great. - You're the best.
(Standing ovation)
Father!
You'd be this thrilled over plum slushes and coffee?
How thrilled will you be if I bring in a catered buffet?
(The flattery is flowing smoothly.)
I realized I'd made a mistake.
The final video isn't even the real issue.
The choreographers learn both routines...
before casting their votes.
I'm crying.
Because he was already catching...
the things I missed,
I think I'm starting to worry.
Keep your head up.
I shouldn't be acting like this.
My plan is that, no matter what,
I need to secure at least five votes...
from the choreographers.
So I approached it strategically.
What I'm aiming for in this film...
is the distinct charm of each choreographer anyway.
For these individual parts,
I'd like to adjust them by discussing them with you all.
I was trying to appeal to them...
so they'd want to do it by carving out the parts...
that showcase their colors.
For this part, I just want to leave it up to you.
(Mission in progress)
(This is the turn of a heels dance major.)
My job satisfaction is at 100 percent.
I'm giving the choreographers a lot of creative freedom.
Since they know their own colors best,
won't they bring out a far more elevated performance?
That's a good one.
Nice.
I liked it because I felt like I was being utilized properly.
I thought he was so sharp...
in how closely he looked at each choreographer.
Instead of recklessly leaving them to their own devices,
it felt like he was pushing each one's abilities to their peak.
Every single character was so memorable.
It was the real flavor of the piece.
- Yes! - Yummy!
- It's fun, isn't it? - Yes!
It makes me feel great too.
But NaiN must have so much on her mind now.
I'm starting to worry.
I'm the type to carefully read the room.
And the reaction to the solo parts was so positive.
"Should I also have a part where I give the choreographers..."
"some freedom?"
I thought like that.
We're going to set the positions for the chorus.
I didn't come in with fixed formations.
Let's just build the formations as we go.
I felt...
pretty uncomfortable about it.
Deciding formations on the spot is fine too.
But...
At first...
Gosh, I'm torn.
Or... Okay. Let's do this.
(Wavering back and forth)
Gosh, I can't decide.
I thought it could end up being a waste of time.
If it were me, I would have prepared everything...
just like NaiN did.
I came completely prepared.
Luckily,
I organized everything last night before going to sleep.
This is so clean.
It looks like a webcomic.
I'm shy.
It looks so neat.
I always map everything out in advance.
Since there were so many micro-movements this time,
I tried to break them down...
into Plan A, Plan B, and Plan C.
I'm a complete J personality,
so I wanted to learn from NaiN.
I'd heard a lot about NaiN...
that she keeps things seamless when working on choreography drafts.
So I'm curious to see it.
I'll teach you the chorus first,
and then walk you through from the top in sequence.
- Great. - Okay.
We're going to start with a hand sign.
Please keep your thumbs horizontally aligned...
and cross the rest of your fingers.
For me, synchronization is...
the most important thing.
Next, on counts 5 and 6, your left arm goes like this.
Aren't we focusing a bit too much on matching group synchronization?
"Don't go above this line." It felt like saying this.
All ten dancers project different auras,
but it felt like she wanted everyone tailored to NaiN's tone.
It's just boring. It's not fun.
It doesn't feel alive.
Honestly, I didn't like it so much.
One, two.
(Just nod along)
The one-dimensional lyric interpretations and things...
weren't pleasing at all.
It felt despairing.
I think I nodded like 30 or 40 times.
Nodding subtly,
nodding to the right,
and then nodding once more in the middle with BABYZOO.
Anyone watching would think I'm the king of positivity.
We'll listen at this tempo once and go back to the original speed.
- Okay. - All right.
What can I do? I just have to do it.
I don't want to become the Worst Director Candidate.
I channeled the Hee Jung from my college days.
Sizing up the room...
sharp and fast.
This is actually the first time we've been drilled...
under this tight discipline.
We don't usually have a chance to be doing this.
Picking everything up so briskly.
But honestly, I thought...
NaiN could pick INGYOO as the Worst Director Candidate.
I think we'll shoot this part at half-speed.
- To match the camera moves? - Yes.
That's cheating!
- Hey. - I just mean...
We're just joking around among ourselves.
It's not that I'm criticizing you.
You know what I mean, right? It's just us.
It looked like NaiN's expression stiffened up.
Want
(Joking around)
Unbelievable.
We might brush it off as a joke,
but if someone doesn't take it as a joke...
and calls it out, it becomes an issue.
I might look a little crazy, but...
Pretty convincing, right?
Isn't it convincing?
It was a way to shift the mood...
and break the tension.
Anyway, I think...
Renan? I'm not sure about Renan.
Hash.
I'm not sure,
but it seemed like Hash was...
struggling to adapt during Koo Young's section.
There seemed to be a lack of active participation.
The premise was...
telling us to develop...
the choreography ourselves,
but honestly, I believe that bringing out the development...
is the director's responsibility.
Depending on how the on-set directing plays out,
I think the outcome will be different.
(The day of the concept shoot)
Hello.
What's this?
Do we have private green rooms?
It's just us?
I see. Okay.
(The 8 dancers arrive at the shared waiting room.)
Since today is the shoot,
we have to showcase our best...
while evaluating both directors at the same time.
So I figured I really needed to stay sharp.
Because they can send me to the Last Stage,
I have to dance flawlessly...
and watch my behavior around them,
so I'm nervous.
Hello.
(All 8 dancers finish checking into the studio set.)
The anxiety and nerves started...
kicking in right away.
If you get on the director's bad side, I'll be doomed.
I need to get my act together.
It's suffocating.
If I get singled out as the Worst Director Candidate,
I'm done for.
I didn't want to leave even the tiniest flaw.
I will become the directors' right-hand and left-hand man.
Please don't pick me as the Worst Director Candidate.
The Last Stage means death for us.
If you get cut right on the first Last Stage,
you'll literally cry tears of blood.
Kasper, did you change your outfit?
Yes. Do you want to take a look?
Yes, let me see.
I'm just going to wear what they prepped for me.
I only kept my own shoes on.
- Good. - Diversity is...
the exact direction...
I'm aiming for.
(During the presentation of the concept)
(Back Koo Young focused on bringing out all 10 characters.)
(Stylist)
(Back Koo Young requested costumes tailored to their own characters.)
NaiN's costumes are like a crew,
while Koo Young's were strictly individual.
I wanted to put...
a sharper spotlight on each individual person.
It's way too flashy, right?
- Everyone looks flashy. - Really?
There was that freedom where I could wear...
whatever I wanted.
- I like this one. - Do you like it?
If you like it, I like it too.
He gave us so many open options.
So, in a way,
that might have been a strategic move.
If you micromanage everything from 1 to 10,
they might not be able...
to showcase their own color and personality.
- Do I look okay now? - Yes.
I like it.
I can tell Koo Young...
definitely prioritizes freedom.
But that vibe...
wasn't quite...
what I personally was aiming for.
I wanted viewers...
to watch comfortably...
rather than feeling overwhelmed and distracted.
It's something they have to watch every single time.
I think mine was better.
We'll proceed with shooting the intro scene first.
(The intro where 10 choreographers reach their hands toward the camera)
Director, I'd like to add an option here.
After filming everyone doing the same move one by one,
I also want to capture individual profile shots for each.
I want to get it done for now.
I don't know which cut we'll end up picking.
That was professional of him.
Securing coverage shots is important.
Once you hit the editing room,
there are countless moments where you wish...
you'd have grabbed just one more shot.
He's someone...
with far more experience and flexibility.
Nice!
You pulled off the chorus so well.
I danced harder than I did for my own piece.
Wouldn't that effortless composure...
rooted in experience...
make people follow...
his lead even more?
I think I was a little nervous.
It's just...
(The filming is temporarily put on hold.)
Can someone come over here and help me out?
- Well... Not MIN JUN. - Who?
Tae Woo.
Yes?
(His sidekick springs into action.)
Yes, Koo Young.
He called me, so I went right over.
- Like an automatic reflex. - Yes.
Yes, Koo Young.
(What is Kasper's mission?)
I pushed down on the cameraman's shoulder...
when he was supposed to go down.
Then I supported BADA.
I was pulling double duty.
Worst?
I have no idea who he might pick.
I always have to stay on my toes.
Let's run a blocking rehearsal among ourselves once.
- Okay. - Okay.
I liked that it kept us on edge.
The actual set is going to be way more hectic.
To properly rein in...
the nine trouble-making choreographers...
having just 1 or 2 obedient guys like me...
isn't going to cut it.
Next team, please get ready.
- Okay. - Okay.
He has to lead us...
and win over the cameraman at the same time.
Director, wouldn't it be better...
to catch this from a low angle right from the start?
I think it'd be great to grab a tight shot once.
I got to see how he communicated with the cameraman today, too.
He even used those technical terms.
Excuse me, but...
About the opening tilt-up...
But definitely, the side with the panel lights...
Terms like "tilt-up..."
and "zoom in."
If you don't know those terms, you know, they look down on you.
It's just like the Dongdaemun wholesale market.
They won't even sell to novices.
Director, do you mind...
if I try operating the camera for a shot?
(Back Koo Young even tries filming the camera take himself.)
Of course, I'm not a pro like the cameramen are.
But I created the choreography, so I know it inside out.
It needs to drop down like this.
I see. So it's okay to move a bit early.
He even took hold of the camera himself.
Now I have to step up and show moments...
where I don't fall behind,
so I feel the pressure.
We'll now roll Take One of the dance scene.
The scene from BADA to BABYZOO, then INGYOO.
- Let's test pulling him up first. - Okay.
(BABYZOO's section features a high-difficulty technique...)
(where he pops straight up off the floor in one beat.)
Five, six.
Seven, eight.
- Jun Hui. - Yes?
- Not like this. - Okay.
Use your core strength to rise in a straight line.
Four, five, six.
Seven.
(Failed)
(On, no.)
- What's the problem? - I'll try it.
I'll get it right.
BABYZOO made some mistakes there.
He's supposed to rise straight up like this,
just like Michael Jackson.
Squeeze your buttocks tight...
and make your core rock-solid.
From the back of your thighs.
You can't let yourself get scared.
- Okay. - If you...
push your hips back trying to keep your balance,
you'll never pull this off.
Okay.
- Let's try it one more time. - All right.
Five, six, seven.
(Failed)
(The 4th attempt)
(The 5th attempt)
I'm so sorry. I'll do it right.
It took quite a bit of time.
Is that hard?
Was it too difficult to pull off to begin with? Just then...
(Back Koo Young ends up demonstrating it himself.)
Seven, eight. Like this.
Do you get what I mean?
(Impressed)
He popped straight up in a clean line.
- How did he do that? - Do you get what I mean?
If you're going to fail, just fall over.
Use your core strength as much as possible.
Koo Young got a bit edgy then.
Please check the time for me. What time is it?
If this doesn't work out,
it causes a delay because of me,
so I wondered if I should've gone up to him...
and asked, "Should we practice this beforehand?"
I think this is an episode that aroused...
because the director placed too much faith in the dancers.
(Back Koo Young didn't practice the technique during rehearsals.)
"They will probably practice in advance."
I think he was too complacent and trusted them blindly.
- Darn it. - Wait. Cut.
(JEONG MIN JUN's mistake)
(The section where JEONG MIN JUN tosses the chair to Kasper)
It was the part where I should roll the chair over.
For me to slide the chair toward Hash,
the camera needs to move a bit faster.
I'm leaving this up to you.
(I'm leaving this up to you.)
Okay.
Stay hidden off-camera...
and slide it right on cue.
(However)
Please!
(Repeated failures)
- Are you okay? - I didn't actually pull it off.
We could have run the chair toss a few more times yesterday.
He could have easily said, "Do you want to run it once..."
"along with the blocking?"
Was the spot where he tossed the chair too far?
(Back Koo Young spots the issue on set.)
It cuts both ways.
Either incompetence,
or placing way too much faith in the dancers.
To put it nicely, Koo Young is...
completely free-spirited.
"Wear whatever outfit you want."
"Dance however you feel like dancing."
But to put it bluntly,
he doesn't come with much structure in advance.
It was like "Do whatever you want."
That might feel comfortable for some,
but for others, it can easily feel like extra labor.
That depends on each person.
That actually felt worse to me.
I think it puts a burden on the dancers.
It feels like homework.
In terms of winning over the choreographers,
I believe my approach might be the more convincing one.
- Good work, everyone! - Yes!
(Director Candidate Back Koo Young's shoot is over.)
- Thank you. - You're the best.
Hello.
(The next Director Candidate NaiN prepares for the shoot.)
I wanted to give off a trendy throne vibe,
so I requested a clean black-and-white look...
so it wouldn't look cheap or flimsy.
(Sleeping makeup)
I took on a style...
completely opposite to earlier.
Do I look sexy?
(Shy)
How was Koo Young's directing?
He's very free-spirited.
It felt like he gave...
each individual the freedom of a soloist.
"Break through your ceiling with your own unique style."
- And NaiN is tightly structured. - Yes.
But honestly, I prefer structured setups.
(Surprised)
There's a distinct thrill that comes from razor-sharp precision.
With NaiN, everything is...
crisp and clearly directed,
so it might have more mainstream appeal.
Actually, we still hold the upper hand...
since we're the ones casting the votes.
If Koo Young says "Minus 2 points,"
I'll go, "What?"
"You're bringing up the points first?"
"You'd better watch out." I think this is what it is.
(Director Candidate 1 can't let his guard down.)
- I predict NaiN's is going... - I know.
To turn out much cleaner.
I drew out...
the camera angles beforehand just in case I might get confused.
I also preset eye-lines for each section.
I mapped out the stage area in advance...
and organized exactly where we'd shoot.
This is for when I become the director.
I came up with some ideas in advance.
Please shoot this one from a high diagonal angle.
(NaiN briefs the cameramen on her draft video.)
You want the final edit to cut...
- like the reference video, right? - Yes.
The angles and timing, completely identical.
So I don't think we need to grab...
multiple coverage shots like Koo Young did earlier.
We will just tackle each shot listed here,
- one by one. - Exactly.
Since we have more cuts than earlier,
if a take is good,
please let me know right away so we can move on.
Koo Young didn't have that many sections,
but NaiN has nearly twice the cuts.
Koo Young only...
broke things down into five one-take sections.
NaiN has double the cuts, but there is barely any blocking movement.
There's no risk for the dancers,
but setting the camera each time could eat up a huge amount of time.
Everything is cleanly organized in my head,
so the real key will be how quickly I can push things forward.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Did you get some rest? - Yes.
- I like your outfit. - I know.
You know how to pull off an outfit.
Our director really knows how to motivate us,
- I mean... - giving out compliments like that.
It's really pretty.
(Energy up)
Are you conducting an orchestra?
- NaiN. - Yes?
I stacked these rings so my hands stand out more.
- Is this okay? - Yes.
I was worried it might look too flashy on me.
- Just make sure they don't fly off. - Okay.
(I'm the only one with rings.)
I just can't handle this.
Since I'm also in a position where I have to prove myself,
I brought out the rings, hoping they'd add...
some extra highlight.
- Give me a ring too. - Which one do you want?
You can choose between these two.
I want this.
I want to wear something glittering too.
- Koo Young wants one. - How about this one?
- How about this? - This...
What if he loses one more ring...
and ends up with nothing?
- Can I try it on for just a second? - Kasper doesn't have one either.
Just for a second.
Stylists! Where are they?
(BABYZOO is left bare-handed.)
Where did they go?
- I should show this one. - They carefully fitted...
four rings to my size, but I lost them all.
The stylists will bring more over.
- Let's all wear a lot of rings. - I'll give all of yours back.
Okay.
How are you feeling, NaiN? Are you nervous?
Yes, a little.
I think it will be fun.
Dancers for the first cut, please step in.
- Thank you. - All right.
For the opening "fight" part, please do it a bit like this.
- "Fight." - Yes. That would be great. Thanks.
You can subtly lip-sync the word "fight" if you want.
Giving the gaze alone is fine too.
Please keep...
our spacing consistent throughout.
Okay. Good.
As soon as I do this,
- you drop in almost simultaneously. - "Simultaneously?"
Yes. Thank you.
NaiN is a monster for details.
(She checks every detail before monitoring playback.)
Good.
Please let the hand be in frame!
(Clean)
- Okay. - Good. Let's move on.
- Thank you. - All right.
Simeez, Hash, please step up.
Okay.
NaiN's choreography is so crisp,
the structure is locked in,
and all the cuts are mapped out, you know.
It makes me think she's like an AI.
I can see NaiN from my room.
The "ai" in her name jumped out at me.
- I was like, "Is she GemiNaiN?" - "GemiNaiN?"
You'll be standing here on your outer foot, right?
You just need to move your entire body as one unit.
Director, could you push in a bit faster than that?
- Okay. - Thank you.
Can you make it feel...
- a bit more like you? - Okay.
- Full power. - Okay.
(NaiN's direction rendering in real time)
Good. Let's move on.
NaiN just breezes through everything exactly as she prepared.
I'm the type who values pinpoint precision.
NaiN suits my style better.
I think NaiN offered clearer direction.
NaiN was a lot better at delivering cues...
that dancers can process intuitively.
Her seamless directing makes me feel a bit on edge.
This is going to wrap faster than my take did.
But the sofa scene is going to eat up quite a bit of time.
Renan has the rolling chair too.
But once they nail it in one go, that's a wrap.
So...
The chair didn't slide as well as I expected.
Watch out.
I think I stayed anxious because of the prop.
It's not sliding.
(Renan drilled the chair routine at every spare moment.)
Props are impossible to control.
They're impossible to control,
so I just have to give my all to what I can control.
I need to get comfortable with this thing.
I've been practicing nonstop to the music,
even down to the timing of kicking it and turning with it.
I practiced really hard, nonstop.
Five, six.
(The sofa scene shoot gets underway)
- Hey. - Goodness.
Too fast.
You're starting a little early.
Five, six.
(Stopping)
(Renan keeps missing the cue)
I think NaiN clenched her teeth there.
Let's try that again.
You need to turn as soon as you start moving.
And when you come over, you can come right up next to me.
Yes.
Renan seemed to have some trouble...
catching the rhythm on set today,
so that was a little disappointing.
The chair isn't supposed to come in right away at the beginning.
It's supposed to be like the draft video.
When we do this part,
- could you shoot it from the front? - Sure.
You've been shooting from the side the whole time.
You need to move over to the side for the staggered timing move.
Please shoot it as close to this video as possible.
INGYOO, what I'm realizing is,
NaiN shot her draft video with a team of dancers...
who already work...
really well with her.
And each of us has such a strong individual style...
that I don't think we're getting the same level of unison.
- As TURNS. - Clearly.
It's designed to be performed by TURNS.
That's what I realize now.
Everyone has to fit into the framework NaiN created.
I wonder how many people...
will actually be happy with that direction.
Could all the men gather in the center, please?
(Dancing, then cut almost immediately)
Great.
(Stops moving)
We're just going to change the setup a little.
Changing to the zoom lens takes about ten minutes, right?
I think it'll take about ten minutes.
We'll change lenses and start at 55.
Good, good.
(One move into the next take, and cut again)
Let's shoot the opposite angle.
We have so many scenes, so it's taking longer.
Great. Let's move on.
Because we kept dancing, stopping, dancing, and stopping,
cutting it here and cutting it there,
we never really got that feeling of building momentum, honestly.
So now we're shooting from above.
Could we go a little higher?
Can you give me ten minutes, then?
- Yes. - Bring in the jib.
She was even asking production to follow the exact shot order,
she'd sent over, so it took an enormous amount of time.
The direction for each individual cut may have been clear,
but when it comes to running the set,
that's not clarity. That's stubbornness.
It wasn't efficient, the energy on set dropped,
and the flow kept getting broken.
The directing style...
and the dancers' energy were almost on the same level.
We could never hit that peak.
After about three cuts, just when we're about to go,
she suddenly went, "That's the cut."
I know you're all tired. Thank you.
- Let's go! - It's fun!
- Let's go! We're almost there. - Let's go!
Five cuts left.
Easy peasy.
With them running out of time,
losing stamina was obviously an issue,
but I also had to fit everything I wanted into the time we had.
I think that really weighed on me.
We had to shoot the group choreography...
when everyone was already exhausted.
And we had to get the slow-motion shots too.
We were shooting the dance in these incredibly short bursts.
And with so many cuts when everyone was already tired,
I think the fatigue was inevitable.
(Simeez crashes during the break.)
She really looks like she's asleep.
Does she have a wireless charger on her back or something?
Honestly, I was pretty upset.
I knew everyone was exhausted, so I kept feeling self-conscious.
But I still had to show that I can hold my own...
as a director.
Everyone, for the ending formation in the straight line...
Can we do another version of that formation?
Is there another cut we can shoot with this camera setup?
Please get it.
- Let's do this. - Let's do this.
You can relax for now.
I could tell NaiN was feeling the clock closing in on her.
Producer, how much time do we have?
How much longer is it going to take?
While waiting,
- should we set the positions first? - Sounds great.
We're running out of time.
It's not over until we get the shot.
It's okay, NaiN.
Since we were really pressed for time,
I needed to get everything wrapped up at the end.
Let's just start from the chorus formation...
and shoot straight through to the end.
Everyone, that's a wrap for us.
(NaiN's shoot wraps after the final shot.)
We were running way over schedule.
I think she got a little overwhelmed by the pressure.
I think a director needs to have a certain commanding presence.
You need to feel like you're really in control of the whole thing.
Koo Young seemed more like he was handling the situation,
while NaiN seemed like she was under a bit more pressure.
She's not really someone with a deep understanding...
of how things run on a set.
And it was probably her first time taking the lead...
and carrying a situation like this all the way through.
As for the direction itself,
I feel like mine might be more convincing.
(NaiN returns to the waiting room after the shoot.)
(She tears up a little.)
It's all right. You did well.
Thank you.
You must have felt a great deal of pressure.
I sure did.
They'll count it against me.
It makes me think about...
how I can respond more flexibly the next time...
I'm in a situation like this.
(The draft video shoots are over.)
Wait a second.
(What is handed to the two director candidates?)
You're really dropping a bomb like this on me?
(Deep in thought)
Did NaiN think it through?
I've decided.
(She's done making a decision.)
(NaiN immediately writes down her pick for worst.)
I'm going to base my vote on today.
(Determined)
(Who did they pick as the Worst Director Candidate?)
(D-Day for the Final Director Selection)
I'm nervous.
- Why did they change the spot? - The chairs!
Why am I next to NaiN?
Back Koo Young versus NaiN.
"Final Director Selection."
My goodness.
Seeing Back Koo Young versus NaiN up there...
made me so nervous. My heart was seriously pounding.
NaiN, do you want it? To be the director?
Of course.
Give the rookie a chance.
(Eyes wide)
(Rookie madness before the final pick)
She's something.
- She's really something. - She's really something.
They put something terrifying up on that monitor again.
How could I not feel pressured? Maybe...
it's bordering on overconfidence,
but I have to believe in myself. What else can I do?
I know I can do a good job too.
There's no way I wouldn't be nervous.
(The two Director Candidates, caught between nerves and confidence)
What do I do?
How am I supposed to choose?
Did you watch the videos?
How are you supposed to choose between these?
It's the decision day.
This is seriously hard.
Who do I pick? I still hadn't decided.
(The two concept videos...)
(released early for the Public Judge vote)
The A, B concept videos we shot...
are going up on YouTube.
I want to see how they actually turned out.
So this is how it came out.
Koo Young is incredible.
This wasn't really about who choreographed better.
The process and the final result can be pretty different.
Seriously, it looks so good.
I think watching the videos might change my mind a little.
I think the video I hit Like on...
and the person I actually choose will be different.
I liked the video because the video itself was good,
but at the end of the day, we're choosing a director.
Those are two different things for me.
I don't think you can judge them only by their directing process.
The final result matters, how well I'm showcased matters,
and how much energy I'm able to bring during the process matters.
I think all of that is important.
The audience doesn't know what happened on set.
If the choreography is tight,
they'll think that person was a good director.
But who did a better job leading the entire production...
is also part of what makes someone a good director.
Personally, I thought both of them fell a little short.
When NaiN ran into situations outside what she'd expected,
it took her some time to deal with them.
NaiN worked hard. She worked hard,
but she lacks the ability to work in sync with production.
(The chair isn't supposed to come in right away at the beginning.)
(It's supposed to be like the draft video.)
(Please make it as close to this video as possible.)
(Can we shoot this part from the front?)
Director.
NaiN keeps going back to her own draft video.
For me, that inability to adapt or take things in...
shows that she's not cut out to be a director.
First of all, Koo Young's video...
turned out badly.
In terms of who directed better or worse,
I thought they were pretty similar.
Both shoots ran behind.
And as far as giving us instructions goes,
there honestly wasn't that much either of them needed to tell us.
So I think I'd choose based on whether the video turned out well,
whether the final product was good.
And Koo Young's came out kind of chaotic.
In terms of the visuals themselves, NaiN's video came out better.
If we're judging pure directing ability, then it's Koo Young.
NaiN wants something that's very controlled and locked in,
while Koo Young wants something a little looser and freer.
With Director Koo Young,
you can really feel his years of experience.
But I like it.
I would've directed like NaiN too.
I made my choice.
I chose this person.
(NaiN versus Back Koo Young)
(Who did the 8 choreographers, serving as dancers, choose?)
This is scary.
Of course, there are definitely things about his years...
of experience that I simply can't match.
But I created a video that makes people want to dance,
so I'm confident.
I genuinely think I can become the Final Director.
I believed they were going to choose me.
(Who will become the Final Director...)
(in the Title Sequence Film Mission?)
(Finally, it's time to choose the Final Director.)
(Between the two, who will become the Final Director?)
I was confident.
Because my piece lets each person stand out and look appealing,
I feel like mine might be a little more convincing...
to these directors.
I am nervous.
But unlike...
Koo Young's visual style,
if they prefer clean, tightly organized...
group choreography,
then I think they might like my video more.
I'm really curious about who you picked.
I just looked at the final result.
The whole point of the process is to ultimately...
create a good result.
I actually went around and casually asked everyone.
- I have no idea about this one. - Is that right?
- No idea. - Is it neck and neck?
(An outcome no one could have predicted)
- No way! - Goodness.
- Aiki! - Aiki!
I'm Aiki, your special MC.
Hello, everyone.
(Welcome!)
Aiki!
Title Sequence Film Mission.
Back Koo Young versus NaiN.
The two director candidates,
each created a piece that showcased...
their own distinct style and directing approach.
Now, with the results moments away...
- Now? - What else is there?
The two Director Candidates...
each chose the choreographer they were least satisfied with...
as their Worst Director Candidate.
We'll reveal the Worst Director Candidate.
We're revealing that first?
- What do we do? - Oh, my gosh.
Wait, all of a sudden?
Could it be...
Worst Director Candidate.
I'd be annoyed right off the bat.
It means they think you did badly.
I'd bawl my eyes out right there.
If you're named a Worst Director Candidate,
I'd say there's a 90% chance you'll go to the Last Stage.
I always give everything my all,
so I don't think I'd be the Worst Director Candidate.
Maybe INGYOO, rather than me?
INGYOO is naturally free-spirited,
NaiN likes everything structured.
So can two complete opposites understand each other? They can't.
I don't think so. I don't think it's me.
As long as it's not me.
How do you even pick someone for elimination here?
It'll be hard. Everyone worked so hard.
I have no idea with this one.
First, Director Candidate Back Koo Young,
please announce the Worst Director Candidate you chose.
(Out of my own mouth?)
(Right after filming, Back Koo Young narrows it down to two.)
With BABYZOO, a few mistakes...
cost us a few takes.
MIN JUN tends to make things too much his own style.
It didn't quite fit.
He didn't blend it.
(Back Koo Young narrowed the Worst Director Candidates down to two.)
(JEONG MIN JUN, BABYZOO)
(Who will be the Worst Director Candidate: MIN JUN or BABYZOO?)
The Worst Director Candidate I chose is...
BABYZOO.
(Back Koo Young's Worst Director Candidate, BABYZOO)
Why? I was so thrown off.
(Worst Director Candidate, BABYZOO)
No way. Why?
Is this for real?
No.
Why? BABYZOO is so good...
so I couldn't help but question it.
During the shoot, BABYZOO...
messed up that get-up a few times...
so we ended up with unusable takes.
What feels a little unfair is...
I got it in 2, 3 tries.
If I were the director and... the dancers were struggling,
wouldn't some of that be on me too?
It wasn't choosing a candidate,
but finding a reason to pick one...
that took me a really long time.
I don't know.
If Koo Young becomes the director...
there's probably a good chance I'll end up on the Last Stage.
Can I really vote...
without any emotion at all under these circumstances?
Then who did NaiN choose as her Worst Director Candidate?
I really have no idea who it'll be.
Oh, dear.
During the shoot, it was Renan and Hash.
(Renan repeatedly missed the timing.)
It felt like Hash didn't give it everything.
(Hash didn't show full potential)
The Worst Director Candidate I chose is...
I honestly wasn't worried.
Her directing style was very similar to what I aim for.
I worked hard...
so I didn't think I'd be the Worst Director Candidate.
I'd be really upset if NaiN picked me.
It's Renan.
(Worst Director Candidate, Renan)
She picked me as the Worst?
I was going to vote for NaiN...
but this makes no sense.
(Worst Director Candidate, Renan)
The chair part was really tough...
If she'd seen how hard I practiced off to the side,
I don't think she would've picked me as the Worst Director Candidate.
I really hope Koo Young becomes the Director.
I think it was because of the chair part.
I think so.
At rehearsals and during filming...
It's nerve-racking because everyone's so good.
One small mistake could make me the Worst Director Candidate.
So I need to stay fully focused.
After NaiN picked me,
I really hoped Koo Young would get it.
I couldn't help but feel that way.
I really don't want to go to the Last Stage anymore.
I hope NaiN gets it.
I really, really hope she does.
The Worst Director Candidates revealed so far...
- are just candidates. - Right.
No one is safe.
The eight choreographers who didn't become Director Candidates...
and the Director Candidate who misses out on the final spot.
The nine choreographers...
will be evaluated by the Final Director and the judges...
to determine who goes to the Last Stage.
The number of choreographers going to the first Last Stage is...
- She's saying it. - Please!
- Please. - Let it be as few as possible.
This is seriously so scary.
Three.
(A total of 3 out of 9 will go to the Last Stage.)
That's brutal. Three people.
Two get eliminated, and only one survives.
That's true.
Only one of the three can survive.
Only one survives.
That's seriously brutal.
That's the cruelest number. The absolute cruelest.
Two go home and one survives. That's what makes it thrilling.
That's seriously brutal.
It's like surviving a fire pit.
They must be desperate.
I just hope it's not me.
I seriously don't want to go to the Last Stage. No matter what.
This is already painful.
I just have to nail everything and give it my all.
As someone who always considers the worst-case scenario,
it's better to prepare myself than not be prepared at all.
Still, I'll stay laser-focused and give it everything I've got.
Will they survive...
or become the star of the very first Last Stage?
I really don't want to be that star.
And the one person who gets the greatest authority...
The director
We will now announce...
the Final Director of the Title Sequence Film Mission.
(Tension)
If I go to the Last Stage as the Worst Director Candidate,
wouldn't that feel absolutely awful?
I have to be the Final Director.
I've come this far.
I don't think I can let this go.
First, let's take a look at...
Director Candidate Back Koo Young's final concept video.
(He means it will be fun.)
- Let's see. - Okay.
But I purposely didn't watch it...
because I thought I'd figure it out.
There's a bit of tension.
I focused on the idea of a film that represents all of us,
and tried to showcase everyone.
I hope that came through well.
Yes!
The intro feels a little lacking.
It might be a little bland.
(The scene that led BABYZOO to be named Worst Director Candidate)
Yes!
The hat is so cute.
I think it came out really clean.
Yes!
Koo Young was neat,
and everyone stands out.
I stood out too.
It opens up space for each person to dance.
There are too many added zoom-ins and zoom-outs in post,
so it feels really chaotic.
I love it.
(Loving it)
It feels too divided up?
In parts that could've had more group choreography,
we split up too often.
And we only dance together briefly in the chorus,
so that was a little disappointing.
You can really see each person.
(Well done, everyone.)
It turned out really well.
I didn't set a strict framework and make them follow it.
With the choreography I gave them,
they developed it in their style.
And in that respect,
I trusted they'd choose me.
The way the choreography transitioned...
felt a bit like what I do.
Comparing the two,
I thought mine felt cleaner and more polished.
I really want it now.
This is going to be so close.
All ten vary in intensity,
style, and the aura they give off.
But she seems to want them all to dance in NaiN's style.
I love this part so much.
Technically, it fell a bit short.
It's something other dancers could've done too.
(The key moment that made Renan a Worst Director Candidate)
The concept had a pillar to kick,
but it wasn't there when I did it.
So of course it was difficult.
It was compact and clean.
It was simply well organized.
It had to feel fresher than mine.
Because hers is way trendier.
Mine felt a little fresher to me.
We went from using mirrors to using acrylic...
NaiN's concept felt like a fresher experience to me.
NaiN's concept video was..
Like a super polished artist demo.
(Agrees)
It came out as well as I'd imagined.
It's clean,
and the camera transitions are really tightly packed.
If they like what I like,
I think they would've chosen me.
I need five director votes.
I think I can get them.
All evaluations are now complete.
The Final Director of the Title Sequence Film Mission...
will be decided without votes from the two Director Candidates,
using the other eight choreographers' votes...
plus one Public Judge vote.
Based on today's result,
the Director Candidate who doesn't become Final Director...
could go to the Last Stage.
I really don't want to go.
It's the worst.
One person will gain authority...
while another faces a crisis.
Who will become the Final Director?
It's not even me. Why am I so nervous?
I don't know. I'm nervous.
Which director candidate will win the Public Judges' vote...
and secure one vote?
Let's reveal it now.
I think the public...
likes NaiN.
Based on the demo,
I liked NaiN's choreography.
I wanted to perform it.
If Koo Young becomes the director,
I'll end up in the Last Stage.
I think Koo Young will be chosen.
The public will vote for him.
I'm a hype meter.
I thought Koo Young's video was nice.
What did the Public Judges think?
It was clean and easy to watch.
There were a lot of well-timed transitions.
"It did a great job of bringing out each dancer's individual charm."
Overall, there was plenty of praise.
(The Public Judges shared various opinions.)
There were a lot of comments under NaiN's video.
Her video had almost 200 more comments.
Title Sequence Film Mission.
Final draft videos.
Based on the views generated by the Public Judges,
Koo Young's video,
has 181,907 views,
while NaiN's...
has 161,622.
Koo Young is currently in the lead.
The views were much higher than I expected.
So I feel like I actually have a chance.
I really want to win the public's votes.
It's making me...
so nervous.
Will the number of likes...
show the same result?
I think more people voted for NaiN.
I'd pick Koo Young's video.
It looks fun.
Let's reveal the number of likes on Koo Young's video.
(Back Koo Young: 8,172)
What? He barely got any likes compared to the views.
Koo Young's video received 8,172 likes.
It made me a little more confident.
Let's reveal the number of likes on NaiN's video.
Let's see.
(Nervous)
(Nain: 15,729)
(Satisfied)
I'm so relieved.
I was happy about it.
I made my plan...
assuming I wouldn't get any votes from the Public Judges,
and set my goal at getting five votes from the other choreographers.
So I don't think that'll be a problem.
That's a big difference.
Yes, it's big.
The Public Judges don't know the process.
Koo Young's video had more views,
but NaiN's video had nearly twice as many likes,
earning NaiN...
the Public Judges' vote.
I was off to a great start.
I think I'm going to win.
Let's see who was chosen by the choreographers.
(Sighing)
Oh, my gosh. I'm so nervous.
First off,
this is INGYOO,
Hash,
and Kapser's choice.
Why did she mention them first?
Does the result depend on us?
Please. I just hope I'm not the last one.
Now, I'll announce...
their choice.
I had to receive five votes from the directors.
I was hoping they'd pick mine.
I'll announce it now.
(INGYOO, Hash, Kasper: Back Koo Young)
(Baek Koo Young: 3 votes)
Koo Young's has better quality.
His draft is the one...
that really showcases each dancer's individual abilities.
You can feel his years of experience.
I felt he could bring all the dancers...
up to a higher level.
That's why I thought his video was good.
That was what I expected.
I did feel disappointed,
but you don't know what will happen yet.
Currently, it's 3 to 1.
Koo Young is in the lead.
Who did the other choreographers...
choose?
I'll announce Renan and MIN JUN's choice.
I contemplated...
until the very last moment.
The video was compact and nice.
So I pressed the like button.
This is the result.
(Renan, MIN JUN: NaiN)
(NaiN: 2 votes)
Renan and MIN JUN chose...
NaiN.
It surprised me.
I had no idea Renan would choose me.
I felt so uncomfortable.
It wasn't a strategy or anything.
Her choreography...
just looked fuller.
I just chose the choreography I wanted to perform.
It's a close game.
Currently, it's 3 to 3.
I'll announce BADA's choice.
Why only me?
(A nervous laugh)
(Feeling awkward)
I think she chose NaiN.
BADA chose...
(BADA chose NaiN.)
NaiN.
I think I watched it with the same perspective as the Public Judges.
Her choreography stood out more and looked cleaner.
BADA's choice...
brings the score to 4 to 3.
NaiN has turned the tables.
What will...
the remaining two votes bring?
I feel uneasy.
Why did they save BABYZOO and Hee Jung for last?
Honestly, I was sure Hee Jung had voted for me.
I made her solo scene stand out.
But I chose BABYZOO as the worst candidate.
(The worst candidate chosen by Koo Young...)
(was BABYZOO.)
What? I was so perplexed.
Can I really vote...
without any emotion at all?
I'm in trouble.
I definitely have a chance to win.
I think BABYZOO...
might've chosen me.
I think my choreography suits him more.
I'm sure he'll vote for me.
Simeez chose...
(Simeez chose Back Koo Young.)
Koo Young.
- It's 4 to 4. - It's 4 to 4.
You never know.
It depends on BABYZOO now.
(Their fate lies in his hands.)
(Will you become a director?)
(Will you remain as a dancer?)
Who did BABYZOO pick as his director?
I'll announce it now.
(It's revealed now!)
(Who is the director of the Title Sequence Film Mission?)
You never know.
It depends on BABYZOO now.
(Their fate lies in his hands.)
(Will you become a director?)
(Will you remain as a dancer?)
Who did BABYZOO pick as his director?
I'll announce it now.
Who did he choose?
If I receive just one more vote,
I'll become a director.
I was so nervous.
My heart was racing.
I really need to be a director this time.
(Which one did BABYZOO choose as his director?)
I'll announce it now.
He chose Koo Young.
(Unbelievable)
What? My brain stopped for a moment.
I couldn't believe it.
I'm very disappointed.
The worst candidate he chose...
chose him.
I feel sorry for him.
I thought I lost.
I was thankful that he trusted me.
That's what I felt.
(Why did BABYZOO pick Koo Young?)
I considered how he communicated with the camera director.
He has a lot of experience.
(He showed his professionalism...)
(by securing some extra takes just in case they were needed.)
The final score...
is 5 to 4.
The director who will complete the title sequence of the show...
is Back Koo Young.
Koo Young's name will be added to the credits as the director.
Ecstatic, right?
(Laughing)
We all worked hard with the same goal...
of becoming the director of this film,
and I'm truly grateful...
that you chose me to represent everyone.
I'll give it everything I've got, body and soul,
during the upcoming shoot...
and do my best...
to make a great film.
- He's so reliable. - Thank you.
Let's go!
I love it.
(Laughing)
Well...
I like it partly because Koo Young...
didn't choose me as the worst candidate.
I'll do my best...
to make sure he's happy with the result.
(Meanwhile)
Rather than being upset,
I had complicated feelings.
I narrowly missed out on winning...
from the very first mission.
(She lost to BABYZOO by just a hair...)
(in the 1-on-1 Signature Mission.)
(She also lost her position as a director in the first mission.)
I'm sure I lost by just a hair, which is very disappointing.
Will I miss out again this time, by just a hair?
I was nervous, to be honest.
(Her name has never added to the credits yet.)
You can't ignore his experience.
There are some areas where I just can't match...
his experience and years in the field.
I think I'll have to figure out...
how to adapt and respond flexibly.
(Koo Young comes back to the room after becoming the director.)
I was thankful that they trusted me.
Once I was chosen as the director,
I felt a sense of responsibility and pressure...
about what I needed to do...
to make the best film possible.
After all that, came the joy.
I can make it well.
I can make them look their absolute best.
I'm sure of that.
I'll make an even better film...
for the final cut.
(Meanwhile in the Square)
(Koo Young's chair is replaced with a director's chair.)
His chair has been replaced with a director's chair.
(Spotting)
Well, there's nothing I can do.
I do feel extremely disappointed.
My position has changed so much.
Now that I'm a dancer,
I need to win his favor.
I'll show him that I'm working hard.
It's clear...
that Koo Young is the real king now.
The nine of us would absolutely hate to become the worst dancer.
I'm sure we'll grit our teeth and give it everything we've got.
I'll work hard as a dancer.
It's time for me to become his favorite again.
I want to support him properly...
so he can move in a better direction.
I was originally his favorite.
I can bring my energy and ideas...
whenever they're needed.
I'll work hard to give him confidence...
through great dancing and a cool vibe.
Yes, Koo Young. Yes, sir.
I'm the number one candidate.
Please call me anytime.
As a dancer, I'm extremely confident.
"I need this part to be more impactful."
"Who is the dancer who is capable of it?"
That's me.
I'm confident in my dancing.
I'm going to show a level of dancing...
that no one else can match.
I want to avoid being named...
the worst choreographer and falling into the fire.
Why on earth? How should I understand it?
BABYZOO worked so hard and did a good job during rehearsal.
His hips spilled out a few times.
I was like, "Could he actually become the worst candidate?"
I was really shocked.
But I'm just the worst "candidate."
When you put that kind of pressure on us,
we're able to keep refining things...
until we come up with something better.
That's one of a director's strengths.
He found my weakness.
That means I should conceal it from now on.
I need to work on my weaknesses...
and create an even bigger wow factor.
All I can think about is making up for what I lost.
"Making up."
I feel so bad...
about choosing someone as the worst candidate.
I feel sorry.
But that's my priority.
I'll have to think about it a lot.
- Oh, no. - No way.
Please change the sound.
It startled me.
Why are you doing this to me?
(I see.)
(Director's seat)
(Running)
(1 second of being a director)
Now, Koo Young is not only a director...
but also a judge.
(Relaxed and chill)
Here comes the director.
(They welcome their director with loud cheers.)
(They don't stop cheering.)
Here comes the director.
I can already feel the taste of power.
- He's different from earlier. - I know.
- Right. - He couldn't even look up earlier.
I'm so jealous of his position.
Where's the red carpet?
(Without hesitation)
(100 points for flattery)
He just earned 100 points.
Hello, it's nice to see all of you, the best choreographers.
I'm Director Back Koo Young.
(Praising Koo Young)
This is the announcement for the best choreographers.
I'm so scared.
As the director, I wanted to commission choreography...
from three choreographers.
I was always the one receiving commissions,
so being the one giving the orders for once...
really made me realize that I became a director.
He won't be both the director and the choreographer.
He'll only direct.
I envied him so much.
The request is...
to create choreography that showcases the director.
Choreography that showcases you or us?
The director.
- We're not directors now. - Oh, right.
We had our director titles taken away for a while.
So Koo Young is the only director now.
The three choreographers...
will present their original choreography to the director.
After the director's final review,
only one choreography will be selected.
The chosen choreographer...
will be credited as the choreographer.
I chose the section of the song.
(Individual Choreography Section)
This is the outro of the song.
(The choreographers must create choreography for the outro...)
(of the title track, with the goal of making the director stand out.)
The outro.
It's the outro.
So they will create choreography for the same section.
It's a competition.
The three choreographers I want to commission are...
I hope he commissions me.
It's my chance to earn points.
Koo Young has never chosen me.
I really hope he picks me.
I'm the only one he chose as the worst candidate.
I think I have to show something now.
The three choreographers I want to commission are...
BADA, INGYOO, and BABYZOO.
I think BADA will bring out unique energy.
I like INGYOO's choreography style.
And BABYZOO knows how to make my choreography work.
If he creates the choreography with me in mind,
I think I'll ll be able to pull it off really well too.
His choreography is absolutely amazing.
Since this choreography will be the finale of the film,
please make it amazing.
I was disappointed that I wasn't included.
As soon as I heard the outro, I was confident.
I'm upset I can't create choreography for that.
I feel like I was given a chance to make up for my mistake.
I'll do my best.
I'll give it my all...
to earn that choreographer credit.
I'll serve him beautifully polished choreography...
on a silver platter,
so he can turn it into something amazing.
Skrr.
The second announcement...
is to create choreography in groups of three...
for the Director's Cut section.
The 9 choreographers will form teams of 3...
and create not only the choreography,
but also the formations and overall staging.
Let me play the music section for you.
(Director's Cut Choreography Section)
(A 7-second section following the 1st chorus)
(Requirement: The car trunk must be incorporated.)
All three drafts will be filmed during the shoot.
After filming all three versions,
the director will select the version that works best...
during post-production and use it in the final film.
So he'll film all 3 groups, but only 1 of them will be chosen.
This is the final announcement.
Additional choreography from the draft may be selected.
If I want to use...
a memorable part of a draft,
I will approach the choreographer,
ask for permission, and use their choreography in the final film.
All choreographers whose choreography makes it...
into the final film through any of the three categories...
will be credited.
What about the others?
Using them as dancers?
Those who do not receive a choreography credit...
will participate in the mission as dancers.
I want to participate as a choreographer.
I want to add my name to the credits.
I want to earn the title of choreographer...
so I don't end up as just a dancer.
That's how I can avoid the Last Stage.
Choreographers and directors are considered to contribute more,
so being credited only as a dancer...
would increase my chances of ending up in the Last Stage.
For the Director's Cut Choreography Section,
please split into 3 groups of 3.
(They start teaming up.)
What do I do?
Should we turn around and wait to be chosen?
Anyone who wants to work with me?
Who wants to team up with me?
You can use my body however you want.
I need to be part of the Director's Cut.
I need to make my presence felt...
to lower my chances of ending up in the Last Stage.
What do I do?
- Oh, my gosh. - So this is how it goes?
They just let us choose like that. I was rather perplexed.
(Reading the room)
We were all trying to read each other.
I was flustered. I'm the worst candidate, after all.
I was like, "No one would want to work with me."
What do I do?
The song is intense. There's no room to breathe.
I'm confident I can deliver intense choreography.
Look at my arms. This part is perfect for waacking.
- I can tell. - I can turn like crazy.
- I can do both. - I can do anything.
- I can do both. - I...
- Dancing, technique... - I can do anything.
I've got it all.
- It's perfect for waacking. - I'll deliver a flashy performance.
You need these moves.
Fast-paced, intense choreography is my specialty.
I mean...
- Why is it so hilarious? - I can deliver intense moves...
in a different way.
They were all trying to convince them.
I didn't want to beg them to team up with me.
I was confident I'd do well no matter who I worked with.
Tell us how you want to structure the choreography.
How about we team up with people who have similar ideas?
Hold on. Let me think.
But it doesn't actually matter.
BABYZOO, MIN JUN, do you want to team up with me?
(What?)
I was like, "This will never end."
So I picked them first.
In moments like that, you have to take the lead.
- Step back. - What?
"What's going on?"
"What? BABYZOO is mine."
Hash, do you want to work with me?
- Sorry? - Do you want to team up with me?
I do. Very much.
I'd love to see how your choreography...
- Me? Let's work together then. - works with my body.
You can do this, right?
- I'll take him. - No.
- I want him. - Okay.
No.
- No. - Come with me.
BABYZOO is popular.
- You choose. - Wait.
Actually, I want him too.
- Wait. - Okay. You choose. Step up.
- I want to work with him. - So it's all of us.
I was just perplexed.
I'm the worst candidate. There's no way they'd choose me.
But I guess they wanted to work with me...
because they saw my potential.
I want to join you.
- Okay. - I want to join you.
I was actually thinking about the three of us as a team.
Hold on. I'm sorry.
- I'm so sorry. - Please come to us.
You know what we can do.
Don't you think the three of us would have incredible chemistry?
- We can do anything. - Yes. We can do anything.
You should bring lots of ideas...
- Wait. - and show them something different.
The timing was perfect.
Hold on.
If I consider how we'd look in the video...
BABYZOO, I'll make it up to you...
for being chosen as the worst candidate.
(Wavering)
No way. He told me to work together first.
He won't betray me.
I need BABYZOO.
I needed BABAYZOO to be in the highlight.
Hash, I'm so sorry.
- Sorry for what? - I want to join the guys.
I think I'll stand out...
- among the guys. - You're sorry?
- I'm so sorry. - You suggested...
- we work together first. - I...
- This situation is... - This is...
terrifying.
It's driving me nuts.
No, it isn't your fault. It's mine.
- I'm sorry. - No, it's not your fault.
As long as we create great choreography, we'll be fine.
(Bitter)
The three of us have very distinct personalities.
Good. I'm confident in my distinct style.
- Let's do it. - Okay!
- The three of us will team up. - We'll work together.
(NaiN, BADA, and Simeez teamed up.)
Shall we...
- The 3 of us? - The 3 of us?
Honestly, I'm okay with anyone.
- We'll make a good one. - Right.
Actually, the choreography is important,
but the positioning of the dancers will be just as important.
For example, if BADA was already in the front during the chorus...
and then comes to the front again later...
You know what I'm saying?
That will feel boring.
We'll figure it out on our own.
- Okay. - We'll figure it out on our own.
Why would you make decisions? Are you a Judge?
I tried to mess with you. What's wrong?
You got triggered right away.
It can be boring for guys to appear during a guy's voice.
During the verse.
I already know what you three will look like.
I wanted to teach them a lesson.
All of that talk is meaningless.
They're a group of three girls.
They're a group of three guys.
We're a group of 2 girls and 1 guy.
We have a lot more we can show.
(Agreeing)
We can feel fresher than them.
Right.
No one can expect what will come from us.
That's better for us.
We can come up with three different pictures.
Renan, Hash, and Kasper.
This is an interesting mix.
Butter, kimchi, and tsuyu.
(The butter, kimchi, and tsuyu mix?)
We must take a different approach.
There has to be a kick.
It ends like this.
- We can do something here. - Right.
We have a great synergy.
We can come up...
with five different ideas.
If there's to be a wow point,
I believe three guys have the advantage.
- We have to have a good plan. - Right.
This is what I think.
You should be in the center, Simeez.
- The two of us feel similar. - Right.
I'll do anything.
I can do anything.
We can do anything.
I feel relieved with this group.
There would be a lot we could show as a group of three girls.
I believe we will be the ones with the killing part.
It's something all three of us are good at.
We want to make it ours.
We still don't know.
(The 3 groups start practicing for the Director's Cut.)
(NaiN, BADA, and Simeez's practice room)
Go up.
We lay on our backs like this.
Climb up the trunk?
Right.
In a feisty way.
Like this.
As girls...
- Sounds good. - That kind of vibe?
We thought that we needed to have...
something beyond the choreography.
- I think this is nice. - Really?
- Nice. - Let's do that.
We planned to draw crowns on our necks.
We thought about bringing up our hair...
to show our necks as a killing part.
Gosh, I love it.
- It looks really nice. - Right.
Are you hiding it from me?
Can I see it?
- Go ahead. - We didn't do anything.
- You didn't do anything? - We didn't do anything.
We're working on it right now.
You just started? Okay.
- Good luck! - They must be done with theirs.
This was what I came up with.
If we start with melting,
we can put our backs against each other.
- Right. - We'll go down.
"Brick by brick." We expressed ourselves...
struggling to build up a tower.
We came up with a part that made us touch each other.
I want to do something others can't do.
But I'm not sure if that will get picked...
as the Director's Cut.
- You're right. - This is what I think.
- We should make it impactful. - Right.
It will be better to make them have to choose us.
While MIN JUN and I danced,
there were jumping parts in the middle.
We worked hard to make those parts look clean.
I'm with BABYZOO and INGYOO.
I believe the vibes of three guys...
will create a new picture.
I'm certain that diverse ideas and pictures...
will be made by us.
- Well, - What do you think?
We're people who can make course meals.
We have to serve everything on one plate.
It's not even a plate. It's a sauce dish.
- Gosh! - What do you think?
Hold on.
What could they be doing?
They're going to come up with something amazing.
(Shall we steal a peek?)
(Let's spy on them.)
(Moving carefully)
(NaiN, BADA, and Simeez's practice room)
Gosh, I like that!
(NaiN, BADA, and Simeez are focused on their practice.)
(Approaching secretly)
(Intrigued)
- Right. - Right.
This part is in the way right now.
I think it will be okay with the truck.
The three girls must be sitting down to do something.
(They figured it out.)
They're going for moves.
It's so obvious.
(Super thrilled)
(But where's MIN JUN?)
Doesn't it block her?
Or, "Tightrope walking."
Should we do something like this?
(MIN JUN took another route on his own.)
(MIN JUN's location)
I watched them as if I were in a spy film.
But...
I wasn't able to really see anything.
(Chuckling)
(The older ones are seeing everything.)
They're totally focused.
(The two become more daring.)
(Watching from the front row)
Were we off?
Shall we take a look? Let's see the overall picture.
(Running away)
- Gosh! - Gosh!
INGYOO?
(They manage to return safely.)
I got it.
They're going to sit on the trunk.
- They're going up. - That's what they're doing.
It didn't really bother me...
after watching theirs.
They were focused on the dancing.
I think we were better with the sizing of the sense of space.
I wonder what Renan and Hash are doing.
They're definitely going to have something fascinating.
Kasper comes up with most of their ideas.
That's what it seems like.
(Renan, Kasper, and Hash's practice room)
I like it.
One, two, three, four.
How does this sound?
I'll film this part with my lips.
It can be used like this.
(The phone lip-sync idea Kasper thought about)
That sounds good.
I love it.
I don't think dancing will be enough.
For example...
We will definitely be dancing.
We will be dancing.
But I want us to dance...
inside a fresh composition and picture.
With the phone,
the tight shot will start with the lips.
We will create the overall choreography and picture.
Even the camera transition was thought of.
- Gosh. - We keep getting new ideas.
There's bad news.
What is it?
Phones can't be used...
along with other props.
I just got a new message.
"What do we do? We have to use it."
"This is bad." This was what I thought.
Should I try to persuade Koo Young?
That sounds good.
Really?
I'll really try to persuade him.
No one will expect this to be done with the phone.
It could be considered a great prop.
We're not dancing with pieces of fabric.
I'll get that sorted out.
Don't worry. Let's put it together first.
If we still aren't allowed to use it,
I'll come back with a backup plan.
It felt like Kasper was trying to lead us.
He took responsibility like a dad.
He felt so reliable.
(Dad Kasper steps up.)
- May I go in, Director? - Yes.
What brings you here?
I'm here to make a suggestion.
Oh, right.
First of all...
Oh, I'm sorry. I crossed my legs.
Where are my manners?
Sitting together like this also bothers me.
(He goes to the floor right away.)
I've thought about this a lot.
So...
(He lets him take the seat.)
There's dancing in the first verse...
and throughout the whole song.
I want to do this.
- I see. - So...
Personally,
I'm a bit against using lip-sync.
I see.
Pretending to sing the lyrics...
is something I don't like.
I didn't expect this at all.
I think it's my role to persuade him right now.
This will just be...
something to set the mood.
This is never the main part.
Hash and I will dance together.
Renan will be filmed separately and edited in.
It's possible for us to dance inside.
I thought there was a need for another angle inside an angle.
I think I can come up with something amazing.
Well,
the location is set.
"The trunk must be used."
A choreography and composition using that.
I wanted everything to be focused on that.
I'm planning to create a performance inside the trunk.
Please allow us to do this.
Please allow us to do this. I'll make it work.
If I allow you to use it,
are you willing to go the Last Stage?
(Eyes of hatred)
(He clenches his teeth.)
Okay!
I'll allow props to be used.
Thank you.
(Deep bow)
I will...
try to make something great.
I fell for Kasper's sad face.
I made a deal with him.
Props can be used.
(You're the best.)
But there's an important point.
Koo Young doesn't really like...
using lip-sync.
This is what I think.
We should get this done quickly...
and try to make an alternative.
- Right. - Right.
Sounds good.
I wasn't sure if Koo Young would...
go with this idea.
I'm feeling a sense of fear right now.
I'm not sure we can carry on with that part.
Even though it might not be his preference,
I must make him like the video.
I felt confident in doing so.
Let's go down first.
Okay.
I'll meet BABYZOO for a while.
Okay. Oh, right!
- He also gave me a message. - Really?
- Let's go. - Let's go.
He sent me a message.
"Could you help me after you're done?"
Actually,
I'm very desperate right now.
(Koo Young chose BABYZOO to become a Worst Candidate.)
I was Koo Young's only Worst Candidate.
I had to earn points from Director Koo Young.
(The three choreographers I wish to ask for a part...)
(are BADA, INGYOO, and BABYZOO.)
And he gave me a chance to come up with the outro.
I had to put my name up on the choreographer list.
My strategy is...
I want to ask you two for a favor.
Performing with you?
Right.
For Director Koo Young,
it will feel different when it's three...
instead of me doing the choreography on my own.
That was why I asked them to help me.
Could you come a bit early tomorrow?
- Sure. - Sure.
I'll treat you two to something really good.
They gladly agreed to help.
I have a lot of good people around me.
I asked them not to tell BADA and INGYOO.
I'm sure they won't.
Where are they?
(Tapping)
- Gosh! - Gosh!
- Thank you! - Thank you!
These are for you.
Gosh, you're the best!
- Thank you. - Well, I want to ask for a favor.
- What is it? - The outro part.
I wondered if the two of you could join me when I show it.
(Startled)
(BADA asked for their help just like BABYZOO.)
Well, I'm fine with it.
We can't tell her, right?
What is it?
Should we not tell her? I think we should.
Right?
(Understanding the situation)
We would love to help you.
Are you helping someone else? BABYZOO?
He asked for our help.
So that was why the three of you were talking together.
(BADA saw the three of them talking to each other.)
We had the same idea.
What's stuck in my head...
is the desire to put my name up in the choreographer credit.
Koo Young never chose me.
Director Koo Young...
(What is Father's decision?)
kept choosing INGYOO.
He never picked me.
I want to use BABYZOO's part.
I have to get permission for Kasper's choreography.
(Back Koo Young asked the others for their choreography.)
I was never asked for my choreography.
I felt so anxious.
If I don't get chosen for the outro,
I was filled with the thought of,
"Will I be the one to be heading to the Last Stage?"
We really want to help you.
We can do really well.
Then don't help BABYZOO.
- What? - Don't help BABYZOO.
- Don't help him? - Yes.
(Startled)
(Mental breakdown)
NaiN! What do we do?
Was she also afraid of ending up on the Last Stage?
Gosh, well...
(Simeez struggles to answer.)
Well...
No! I was joking.
No. She wasn't joking.
I was going to take them away from him,
(Laughing)
but that isn't fair.
If I express my style with the same dancers,
I believe I have a better chance.
I'll be performing it with two amazing women.
I'm full of confidence.
It wasn't important.
Instead of having to quickly input my ideas to someone else,
I thought it would be more appealing...
if I could express it on my own.
(D-Day of the outro choreography reveal)
INGYOO hasn't come.
(INGYOO's room is empty before the choreography reveal.)
Is INGYOO sick?
- He's running late. - Gosh.
Whether it be a choreographer or dancer,
there can't be insincerity or tardiness.
Do we get to take a break?
Yes.
(The choreographers fall asleep while waiting for INGYOO.)
The ones who become a hindrance at the site.
I cannot stand those people when I'm the director.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, MIN JUN.
(Bowing down)
(The back of his head is full of rage.)
He seemed to vent his anger.
- INGYOO! - I'm so sorry.
Was your phone off?
Yes.
I've never seen a jerk like him bow down so low like that.
Get up.
I'm so sorry.
Get warmed up for the reveal, okay?
- Right. Gosh. - Right.
Being late? That's a nonstop ticket to the Last Stage.
INGYOO deserves to go to the Last Stage.
I was going through an exhausting schedule.
I forgot to charge my phone and I missed the alarm.
I felt very sorry.
Please gather up, directors.
- Gosh! - Gosh!
Gosh, it feels intimidating.
Hello, choreographers. This is Director Back Koo Young.
(Welcoming the director)
Hello.
(Feeling nervous)
Out of the nine choreographers in front of me,
I asked three choreographers to come up with the outro.
We will check the outro parts now!
(The time has come.)
Let's go!
(Screaming)
I didn't become the director. I can't be Dancer One.
To avoid the Last Stage,
I had to get the title as choreographer no matter what.
I feel really desperate right now.
Putting my name up on the choreographer credit...
is my current goal.
- Let's start with BABYZOO. - Right.
Could you give us an explanation of your choreography?
First of all, I thought that you had to stand out.
To express Director Koo Young's...
good musicality,
I added some acting parts.
I don't really like acting parts in the outro.
It doesn't seem like a good match with the outro.
I asked NaiN and Simeez for their help.
I thought they could help me express my part even more.
I'm confident that it will be impactful.
Being expressive is my strength.
Don't miss it, bro!
Don't miss it, Koo Young.
(How will BABYZOO's outro part look?)
There were many interesting parts.
Hey!
I liked the engagement that could be felt from his face.
The moves felt quite small.
(So clean)
(Impressed)
That was impressive.
I was startled by the great part he came up with.
The musicality was great.
He expressed different textures.
That made the music sound clearer.
Just like BABYZOO mentioned,
it was a part that emphasized the musicality.
But when considering this as the ending,
the moves felt rather small.
When this is seen in a bigger picture,
I have a bit of a concern...
if this part will be captured by the camera well.
He basically meant I took the wrong direction.
I had to think of the big picture,
but I went the other way.
But if this is a mission to make the director stand out,
I still think it's right for the director to do...
something they are good at.
I have a similar opinion with what Koo Young mentioned.
It felt like a part that would look better...
for a smaller group than a larger group.
It didn't feel satisfying to be the ending.
We will check INGYOO's part.
(Second outro part reveal, INGYOO)
Let's go, INGYOO!
- Let's go! - Please get ready.
Yo!
I was excited to see INGYOO's part.
He always came up with great parts.
Actually, I was quite concerned about INGYOO.
(During the signature choreography match)
(Koo Young liked INGYOO's choreography.)
(I love it.)
Whatever INGYOO came up with,
I expected Koo Young to like it.
My part is delicious.
I can already see myself filming for it on my own.
Please give us an explanation of your part.
My choreography was based on what Koo Young mentioned earlier...
about the scale of a large group.
I created this part with the thought of a wide angle.
I'm a creator who fulfills everyone's needs.
I went for Koo Young's needs this time by...
He seems to like my choreography style.
I added everything tasty to fit him perfectly.
I will start!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
I personally like his choreography and composition.
I was excited and curious.
Yes, sir!
Wouldn't my part get chosen?
The impactful parts made it more interesting.
He expressed catchy parts from the simple rhythm.
He knew when to stretch out and get tight.
(Right here)
Cut transition!
Oh, the cut transition?
(Give me)
Thank you.
I preferred INGYOO's part.
I wanted to dance those free moves.
It looked like a fun part to do.
I thought it was a party.
I thought it was a party at first,
but the moves became powerful toward the end.
That was when it got my attention.
Director Koo Young might go with this one.
As INGYOO mentioned,
he has considered the bigger picture.
The musicality was kept within that frame as well.
I was impressed by that.
It was the ending,
but it felt slightly mild.
I...
(What is he about to say?)
can come up with a part every 30 minutes!
(Laughing)
(He promotes himself all of a sudden.)
- Nice. - This took you 30 minutes?
I think it took around that much.
I wasn't trying to be boastful. I promoted myself.
I thought that INGYOO came up with a great part,
but it didn't seem to go with the flow.
I wasn't sure what he wanted to express.
INGYOO's part was abstract.
It didn't feel like an outro.
I did pretty well.
(Satisfied)
Lastly, we will check BADA's part.
(Last outro part reveal, BADA)
Let's go!
I asked Simeez and NaiN for help.
Instead of doing it on my own,
I wanted to show him that it was a part...
that looked better when performed as a group.
They're even dressed the same. That's crazy.
In order to look in sync,
I thought that we had to dress similarly.
I can't believe it.
Please give an explanation of your part.
I was focused on two things.
How it looked together and how it looked for you.
I thought about what would be more impactful...
and make you stand out more.
That was my main focus when coming up with this part.
Also,
Then I wanted to add a bit of my own dance flavor to it.
I tried my best to balance the two elements.
Her long arms and legs give her dancing a unique vibe...
that drives up the energy.
She was one of the dancers I was excited to see.
I'll do my best to get my name up on the Credit Board...
as a choreographer.
(Impressed)
As soon as I saw the first part, I thought...
her choreography was well-structured with key moves.
She owned the rhythm...
and elevated the energy with her big movements.
This is crazy.
(Approving)
I thought she did a good job with her choreography.
She nailed the texture.
And she knows how to make her moves stand out.
I still remember this move in the beginning.
This move for "give me" is also memorable.
Her choreography had many memorable parts.
You kept the rhythm really simple for the ending.
I thought...
that decision gave us a much more direct connection...
to music, so it was a plus for me.
I liked your overall choreography including the key moves.
You put together an unforgettable choreography.
So I really liked that.
But simplifying the rhythm for your routine...
might have cost you...
some of the detailed textures in your moves.
It was disappointing, but there was nothing I could do.
I was looking forward to her choreography.
The musicality was too simple, perhaps.
It's disappointing.
(Back Koo Young is reviewing the choreography...)
(before the final decision.)
They're such good dancers.
Hee Jung and NaiN should get an award.
(Thinking)
BABYZOO's choreography was great too.
This is so fascinating.
I'm writing down the evaluations for these three.
They're all connected.
They feed into each other, forming a complete cycle.
I like her choreography. It's nice and powerful.
But it's lacking texture in her movements.
BABYZOO's movement texture is great.
But it falls a bit short when looking at the overall scale.
INGYOO's choreography delivers a good sense of scale.
But it's too plain.
Their strength and weakness are too distinct.
I'm really torn.
I think I'm going to win...
because my choreography is special.
Please let me win. I'm really looking forward to it.
I'll probably...
go to Last Stage without this win. I'm serious.
I'm worried.
I don't know which way Koo Young is going to lean...
when he makes his decision.
I just put together a bombing choreography for him,
so he could pick me.
I might have a chance to win.
If I'm the first one to get eliminated from Last Stage,
then this place...
will turn gray.
Everything will look bleak.
I worked really hard to get picked by him.
I want to put my name as a choreographer on the board.
(Which one of them will get to put their name on the board?)
Guys.
- Let's practice and get this done. - Okay.
So what else do we need to work on?
- This will be our formation. - Okay.
- Five and five here. - Okay.
Mark your spots.
Everyone is great and working hard.
They learned the choreography beforehand.
I was really happy that our practice session went smoothly.
I'll do my best to be a good leader at the shoot too.
(The day of the shoot for the Title Sequence Film Mission)
(Everyone is getting ready for the shoot.)
(What's about to unfold on set today with the scale dialed up?)
- Gosh. - This is the set.
This is huge.
(Impressed)
They did a great job with the lighting setup.
It's beautiful.
It's definitely going to look massive on camera.
It delivered a huge sense of scale.
The truck had a strong presence on set.
I thought it was going to look so cool.
But the thing is,
we never know.
The video we film today...
might send me to Last Stage.
I cannot make a mistake.
I have to nail the choreography.
I'm a bit worried whether I can faithfully follow...
the directions from Koo Young...
without getting negative feedback...
and still pull off a good performance.
Which way is it? This?
It's this way.
(Simeez asks BABYZOO which way to turn her head.)
(Trembling, frozen)
(What did you say, Simeez?)
How could you ask a question...
about the choreography on the day of the shoot?
How is that possible? What do you think about that?
I was terrified.
It felt like a nightmare was creeping up on me.
I'm in trouble.
My name isn't on the board as a choreographer.
So I need to work really hard today.
When we're filming today,
I need to observe closely who I want to send...
to Last Stage.
Let's film the outro.
(The sun has gone down, and they start filming the outro.)
I asked the following choreographers...
to come up with the outro choreography.
BADA.
(Choreography by BADA)
BABYZOO.
(Choreography by BABYZOO)
INGYOO.
(Choreography by INGYOO)
The choreography I selected is...
(Whose choreography was chosen among the 3 choreographers?)
I chose BADA's choreography.
It's the choreography I can execute well.
And it was a better fit for the ending.
Choreography contribution is a key part of my evaluation.
- Her choreography was chosen. - One,
- two, one. - So she'll get points for that.
Then the odds of her going to Last Stage might go down.
You know?
(Outro Choreographer, BADA)
I won!
It's a high-stakes mission...
because elimination is on the line.
I was so happy that I got my name on the Credit Board...
as a choreographer.
I was bummed out.
I was a bit disappointed that mine didn't get chosen.
She did a great job with her choreography,
so I understood his decision.
I really want to add this move from your routine.
Really? Okay.
(BABYZOO's routine included a collar-biting move.)
I added a key dance move from BABYZOO's choreography...
- to the chorus. - Thank you.
I was grateful.
He's using one of my moves.
Does it mean I'll get credited for it?
Will my name be on the board?
No way.
(While getting ready to film BABYZOO's chorus choreography...)
Hee Jung can't do this.
Simeez and Hash can't do it.
The same goes for Renan.
What do you mean?
This move.
(Koo Young selected the collar-biting move...)
(from BABYZOO's choreography.)
(The chorus with BABYZOO's choreography)
I didn't think this through and failed to see that...
it wouldn't work with their outfits.
He checked the outfits on the day of the shoot.
"What do we do if they're not wearing a jacket?"
BADA, you're in the center for this, right?
I thought I could make it work if BADA who was in the center..
Could execute...
the collar-biting move.
When I got to the shoot,
I saw sharp metal zings on her collar.
It won't be safe.
The metal zings on the collar would scratch me.
- They're really sharp. - Yes.
I didn't want to risk her safety for it.
Or how about holding the collar out? Just to show the vibe.
I showed him another option.
If even one of my moves got chosen for this,
my name would go on the Credit Board.
That's what was at stake for me.
No. I don't want to use this...
- unless we can bite the collar. - Wait.
The director wanted us to bite the collar no matter what.
Without that, this won't work.
The biting part is the key.
He knew that our outfit would come into play.
The fact that he checked the outfits on the day of the shoot...
didn't make sense.
Let's go with this instead.
- Okay. - Okay.
My hands were tied. There wasn't time...
for me to keep pushing for it.
"Does it mean my name won't be on the Credit Board?"
I couldn't be self-serving at the shoot.
Considering my position,
it was just disappointing.
Of course, this is disappointing.
If I were in his shoes,
I would've been so disappointed.
Having your name on the board...
will be a major difference.
But we had to keep filming.
We didn't have much time either.
I just decided to do my best.
That was my focus then.
First group, could you wait over there?
- Okay. - Okay.
(The first scene starts with BADA and shows BABYZOO getting up.)
(But Kasper is in BABYZOO's spot.)
(And BABYZOO is monitoring the scene.)
(Their places have switched. What happened to them?)
BABYZOO's part is my favorite.
I took BABYZOO's part which I liked...
from NaiN's choreography.
- It's really cool. - Okay.
I love that part. So...
Kasper will take BABYZOO's part where he was supposed to...
- get up from the floor. - Okay.
I was relieved...
because...
To be honestly,
that was a difficult one for me.
Five, six, seven, eight.
I'm sorry. Let me try again.
I'm sorry. I'll do it better.
This morning, we had to pull him by the bottom...
Koo Young picked me as the worst. Maybe, he felt bad.
I really don't know.
Anyway, I'm really grateful.
He gave me a part I could execute so much better.
I'm so grateful.
I think he helped me, so I could redeem myself.
I really think so.
Five, six, seven, eight.
(Kasper gets up on his first try.)
(Embarrassed)
I did well, didn't I?
But will this really help his case?
(Sounding cryptic)
(Messing it up)
(They continue filming.)
(Koo Young seems unhappy.)
I think Renan is off the beat.
He's actually saying that out loud as he walks over?
My gosh. If I were in her shoes...
I was scared.
Renan.
You're off the beat.
This part?
- This has to go fast too. - Okay.
- Your tempo is off. - Okay.
(She has to stop on the beat.)
Having a director tell you that you're off the beat...
is a huge problem.
Renan took a long time to finish her scene.
(He watches Renan film with a serious look on his face.)
(They film the same scene again.)
Renan. The thing is,
your movements aren't on the beat.
This is what you're doing.
(He's giving her the same direction again.)
That's what you're doing. Watch.
Renan couldn't dance on the beat.
I went over to her several times to give her directions.
I'm disappointed too.
I'm always disappointed when I perform as a dancer.
- I gave every possible direction. - Just balance it.
I gave directions to everyone.
Some dancers executed my directions on their first try.
Or some pulled them off on their 2nd or 3rd tries.
So that was the difference.
As for his evaluation criteria,
I think he focuses on the level of execution at the shoot.
So I felt bad for her.
Gosh, I'm doomed.
My choreography or any of my moves got chosen.
And he gave me negative feedback at the shoot.
The only shot I have left is the Director's Cut.
I need to get chosen for the Director's Cut.
If I at least have that,
I would feel a little safe about my position here.
We'll start filming for the Director's Cut.
This is driving me crazy. I have to win the Director's Cut.
Without this, I might end up going to Last Stage.
Please!
I'll go to Last Stage without this win for sure.
I'm pretty sure it will be me.
I have to win it no matter what.
We must secure it...
because it gives us the benefit...
that the director is happy with our performance.
So that might lower our chance of going to Last Stage.
Kasper, Renan, and Hash. You will go first.
It's a mystery what they'll do for the Director's Cut.
I have no idea what they're going to do.
I'm going to lie down here.
(Kasper lies down on the trunk.)
And then...
What?
- What? - The camera...
(They can't stop laughing.)
Their use of props was quite unique.
He put his phone in front of his mouth.
He replaced his mouth with the phone.
When I lie down and have the phone in front of me,
it looks like I'm dead and lifeless, but my mouth is rapping.
I was looking for a new angle or a new structure.
I tried to come up with an interesting structure.
We have to study Koo Young's reaction.
He's laughing.
So far, it's funny. Hold on.
I wonder how they'll incorporate this idea into the performance.
He loves anything that's unique and out of the box.
So I respect him for it.
Go all the way over there.
- And Renan will grab the camera. - Okay.
Let's do it one shot at a time.
We start with a close-up shot of my lips.
Hash and I are going to perform the choreography.
It will look like Renan is dancing on the tips of Hash's toes.
So we'll express the lyrics through our moves.
- They overthought this. - The rehearsal...
It's a short part.
They're trying to express all the lyrics.
So the moves don't pop.
They haven't let go of their greed yet.
Too much stuff is going on.
We added a lot of transitions, angles, and effects...
even though our part was pretty short.
I like following the flow...
showing the performance in various angles.
They had a fresh take on it.
It made me see that Kasper had the ability to come up with...
original ideas and tackle the mission...
with a goal-oriented mind.
But it would've been good if they focused more on the dancing.
With three girls on the truck,
they're giving off the queen vibes.
They went with a feminine approach.
- Can you show us in real time? - Yes.
- We need to know how to time this. - Sure.
(They begin the rehearsal to check the angles.)
So pull out after that.
Their performance was predictable.
I knew NaiN, BADA, and Simeez...
would accentuate their feminine side.
But I'm not sure if this sexy concept fits here.
They have the risk of giving off "Street Woman Fighter" vibes.
They should show us something creative...
only directors can pull off.
But their performance didn't leave an impression.
We thought about drawing a crown on our neck.
So we could lift our hair to show the crown.
And that could be our highlight.
We have to do more than just dance for this. We have to kill it.
And the key point would be the crown.
We wanted to do something only we could do as female dancers.
We thought...
if the three of us crushed it with a powerful choreography,
it would work.
(Impressed)
Nice and neat.
The three of them definitely had their own presence.
Cut. That was great.
- Play it. - Let's play it.
They're clapping.
- Okay. - Did they like it? Really?
The response during the shoot is most important.
We were the only group people clapped for.
But who knows?
I don't think their scene left that much of an impression.
But on the flip side,
our performance includes action-forward elements.
We crafted a routine, centering around our teamwork.
A routine that brought us closer.
It's something other groups can pull off.
But it's something we can execute perfectly.
(BABYZOO, INGYOO, and MIN JUN start filming the Director's Cut.)
They actually included some contemporary vibes.
They heavily incorporated contemporary elements.
But considering the progression, would that be a right fit?
Would that be a wow factor of the choreography?
That was questionable.
Rather than going all-out from the start,
opening with a restrained tone would work much better.
It's like an intermission.
We thought physical contact was a great idea.
So we went with the freestyle vibe with physical contact.
We kept it simple with our tiptoes. And for the seamless connection,
we added a transition effect.
It didn't look like anything they've done before.
I find it quite interesting which wasn't expected.
Hey.
The jumping part was the most memorable for me.
It was a new idea.
We tried to make it look like a scene in an action movie.
When we had to use the truck as our prop,
I wanted to portray a scene...
where we jumped off a running truck.
That's good.
The jump scene was cool.
When it came to highlighting the music,
it was a good approach.
Looking at other groups' Director's Cuts,
I think ours is quite special.
I think my group is going to win.
For any choreography to shine, there has to be...
a creative side.
All three groups had great ideas.
Their styles are all different.
I have to consider the overall flow before making my decision.
- Good work! - Good work!
Great job.
I gave my all to every single scene.
I worked harder for this than I would do for my own project.
I gave my 100 percent.
I was practically his assistant.
I wasn't worried.
I don't want to go to Last Stage.
I don't want to go to Last Stage for this mission.
Who is it going to be?
Three of us will go to Last Stage. That's a lot.
A third of us will be up for elimination.
I wonder who it's going to be.
(Anxious)
People whose names aren't on the Credit Board...
might be facing the possibility of getting eliminated.
Getting credited only as a dancer makes me nervous.
It means I have a higher chance of going to Last Stage.
I'm too nervous to do this.
I think BADA is totally safe.
BADA was the only one whose choreography was chosen.
(BADA's choreography for the outro was chosen.)
(I got picked!)
Oh, my gosh!
And she taught the dancers too.
Well, that does it for her.
Gosh, she's safe.
And she totally nailed this too.
I'm nervous.
I'm 100 percent sure it won't be INGYOO.
He's good at everything he does.
If my group wins the Director's Cut, I'm safe.
If we don't, I won't be safe.
I got the chorus.
But that might not be enough to guarantee my survival.
The Director's Cut will be important.
I agree.
If your group wins the Director's Cut,
I'll start thinking that I'm in big trouble then.
I'm in bigger trouble than you are.
I was chosen as the Worst Candidate.
(The Worst Candidate chosen by Director Back Koo Young was...)
(BABYZOO.)
If I don't win the Director's Cut,
I'll go to Last Stage without this win for sure.
I think the one on the right will probably go to Last Stage.
Totally, right?
Renan barely got any parts.
Right.
I don't have a lot of parts in the routine.
They'll judge based on the video.
I'm barely in the video.
Kasper was...
such a good assistant to Koo Young at the shoot.
So he might have earned a lot of points for that.
But all of my parts are a bit iffy.
My position is really iffy.
Renan, MIN JUN, and Kasper. That sounds about right.
I'm considering the possibility that I might be the Worst Choreographer.
Hash didn't get a lot of parts.
Oh, no. What am I going to do? I'm so nervous.
I think the judges' evaluation...
will matter more than...
Koo Young's.
Wouldn't they focus more on the dancers who stand out...
when they watch the video?
- Hello. Nice to meet you. - I'm Sean.
- Very nice to meet you. - I'm Koo Young.
- Nice to meet you. Yes. - Koo Young?
Welcome to Korea.
Thank you.
(Sean Lew is a globally recognized director.)
(The judges greet each other enthusiastically.)
(The winning crew of "Street Woman Fighter" in 2021)
(The leader of HolyBang, Honey J)
(She established herself in the dance scene...)
(with her impressive dance skills.)
(Her unique artistic vision as a director...)
(stood out during the mega crew performance.)
(Honey J was the general director...)
(during the Mega Crew Missions in Seasons 1 and 3.)
When did you come to Korea?
- Three days ago. - Three days.
(The first Asian dancer...)
(to win in the hip-hop category in Juste Debout)
(The world-class battler with 22 years of experience...)
(who conquered the globe)
(It's Kyoka.)
So this sounds like what we did for the second mission. Right?
I remember being completely focused...
when I was filming my Director's Cut.
(Let's do one last time.)
And I was aware that we could show the director...
how desperately we were trying to execute the performance.
I feel like with any video project, it's just really important...
to understand the story behind...
whatever is being shot.
Every dancer, the way they're dancing,
where they're dancing, and why they're dancing.
And that plays along with screen presence...
which I think is going to be really important to catch.
My heart is pounding.
We'll win the Director's Cut, right?
We'll win it.
- We must. - We must.
Koo Young didn't use any moves from my routine.
If I can't win the Director's Cut,
I'll be in big trouble. I'll go to Last Stage for sure.
If we win the Director's Cut,
I'll probably be safe.
- I wonder which one he chose. - I have no idea.
Objectively speaking, ours looks pretty good.
Just dancers?
No, I can't let that be.
I just want to get it over with. I want to see how it came out.
- Right? - Yes.
He's here.
(Utterly nervous)
In the Title Sequence Film Mission,
you had to prove your talent with your choreography...
and compete to get your name on the board.
Gosh, I'm nervous.
Those who failed to prove their talent...
through their choreography...
will receive one last chance to prove themselves on stage.
It's called Last Stage.
There are nine choreographers here.
Three of you will head to Last Stage.
The nerve-racking feeling and the anxiety...
started to hit me already...
when I hadn't even been eliminated.
I don't think I contributed a lot to this mission.
I don't want to go to Last Stage.
The number of choreographers...
who can return to the Directors' Lab after surviving Last Stage...
I couldn't stop feeling nervous.
Is just one.
It was shocking that only one person survived.
I think it's really cruel.
I really don't want to go to the Last Stage.
To determine...
who would ultimately survive and preserve their name,
Director Back Koo Young gave...
the participants the opportunity to have their names listed...
as choreographers on the Credit Board...
during the process of completing the final title sequence film.
The first choreographer Back Koo Young chose was...
BADA.
It is the title I wanted to win the most.
So, I think I'll get a high score...
for my creative contribution.
Secondly, Director Back Koo Young...
personally selected the choreography...
he wanted to use in the final film from the initial draft videos.
The choreographers are...
NaiN and Kasper.
I'm jealous.
BABYZOO's choreography was also selected,
but ultimately failed to make it onto the credit board.
My choreography wasn't included,
and the choreography for the outro wasn't selected either.
I have a feeling the Director's Cut will change my destiny.
The recipients of all the credits have not yet been decided.
It's because the most important choice still remains.
That is...
the Director's Cut.
(Director's Cut Revealed)
- Gosh. - Revealed?
Goodness.
Even if I'm not chosen,
I'm curious about how it turned out.
Who will be the star of the Director's Cut...
chosen by Director Back Koo Young?
Please.
- Gosh. - Goodness.
Title Sequence Film Mission.
Let's watch the final video.
Please.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
(Royalty)
(Synopsis and Film Directionality)
Let's go.
Yes.
(Director Back Koo Young enters.)
Why do I feel so embarrassed?
That's so cool.
(Focused)
How does he get up so effortlessly?
I was nervous.
NaiN is so pretty.
I danced until it felt like my whole body was shattering.
- Nice. - Yes.
It's very clear. I feel like it's really important.
Yes.
(Oh! BADA)
As expected, BADA is incredibly skilled...
at expressing herself.
- Yes. - Hey.
Renan lacked impact in that scene.
(Heelmeez!)
The one wearing heels is amazing.
- Hey. - Hey.
I was just into myself.
The video is thrilling.
(Look at his eyes.)
- Hey. - That's good.
I gave my absolute best in every single scene to ensure...
they would dare choose me as the worst choreographer.
Here it comes.
(Here comes the Director's Cut.)
(Group Simeez, NaiN, BADA?)
(Group BABYZOO, JEONG MIN JUN, INGYOO?)
Wait.
I was about 80 percent certain that we would be chosen.
Please. If I'm not chosen,
I have to do the Last Stage.
I think I'll only feel at ease...
if I get chosen for the Director's Cut.
Wait a minute.
Who is it?
(Director's Cut Revealed)
(Director's Cut, BABYZOO, JEONG MIN JUN, INGYOO)
It was a matter of life and death.
It was really thrilling.
I'm doomed.
(So close)
This is driving me nuts.
(Director's Cut, BABYZOO, INGYOO, MIN JUN)
No!
Will this actually count as a plus?
I'm so embarrassed.
(Simeez is awesome.)
The dopamine rush was off the charts.
Gosh.
Simeez's part is essential right here.
Hey!
- Yes! - Hey!
This is cool.
(Kasper's favorite part, nodding)
I can nod anywhere.
Yes.
We're cool.
NaiN.
I looked good.
NaiN is so good.
She's gritting her teeth.
- Let's go. - Hey.
The director is so cool.
There is an energy that comes from Koo Young's choreography.
It makes you excited.
- Gosh. - Yes.
(You can watch the full video on "The CHOOM" and "Mnet Plus.")
(Wow)
("Royalty" by Yoonmirae and Tiger JK...)
(is available on various music streaming sites.)
It's so cool.
Thank you.
- I want to give you a ten. - I know. I can't give you a ten.
It doesn't make sense.
Thank you.
(The Title Sequence Film satisfied all the Fight Judges.)
Achieving this level of quality in such a short time is impressive.
I love the coloring.
I like some of the transitions. I think it's very clever.
And the mirrors. I think it's really great.
Throughout the video, I caught glimpses of the emotions...
or expressions of each person wanting to take first place.
Since it was a title sequence,
I put a lot of effort into capturing shots...
that would deliver real impact during the editing process.
Guys.
(The 3 happiest people right now)
The choreographers of the Director's Cut...
chosen by Director Back Koo Young are...
BABYZOO, INGYOO, and JEONG MIN JUN.
- Congratulations. - I'm jealous.
(Bitter)
I was really happy.
I thought I might be able to move further away from being the worst.
I was very relieved.
I won't go to the Last Stage.
I'm jealous.
Things aren't going the way I thought they would.
It's a huge shame.
I want to know why.
I chose this cut...
because it effectively captures both a clean aesthetic...
and creativity.
(Agreed)
Even without the lyrics,
the mise-en-scene effectively captures...
the mood of the music.
In the case of BADA, Simeez, and NaiN,
the choreography features slow tempos and transitions.
The performance is flat and lacks impact.
It didn't look right.
It was like oil and water.
- You know. - Right.
In the case of Kasper, Hash, and Renan,
holding the phone in the mouth...
turned out to be not bad at all.
Like this. You know, it's not dance,
but it's a moment. It's a frame. It's a feeling.
I feel like the lip sync thing... I don't know.
I like weird stuff.
I like weird dance ideas specifically.
That's why I kept thinking.
Ultimately, the reason I chose it...
was the expressive ability shown as a dancer.
That played a major role in the decision.
Yes. It makes sense.
With this, the choreographers for all credits...
in the Title Sequence Film Mission have been determined.
The choreographers...
who did not make it onto the Credit Board...
for this mission are Renan, Simeez, and Hash.
What are we going to do?
Hash. Renan.
Did they do this on purpose to send us to the Last Stage?
Goodness. I'm so nervous.
This is bad. I might end up going to the Last Stage.
However,
having your name on the Credit Board...
doesn't guarantee survival.
Really?
Thank goodness.
Please.
This is too hard. Stop.
Nobody knows the future.
So I'm very anxious.
It could be me.
You can't let my guard down.
Now, all that remains is...
the announcement of the final result to determine the choreographers...
who will go to the Last Stage.
My goodness.
Seriously.
I'm getting a touch of PTSD.
I was the worst choreographer.
("World of Street Woman Fighter," Leader Rank Mission)
(It's Honey J of BUMSUP.)
(Honey J was singled out as the worst.)
I was deeply hurt by being singled out.
Today,
I'm in a position where I have to hurt someone.
I think I'll feel sorry while judging the dancers.
Still, I'll do my best to evaluate them.
I think I'll be leaving.
Me too. I think.
(No one can rest easy regarding the result.)
Who will head to the Last Stage?
Director Back Koo Young...
will deliver...
the result personally.
- What? - Gosh.
Oh, my gosh.
He must be having a hard time too.
He's here. I think he's here.
(Really?)
(Is he here?)
(Director Back Koo Young enters.)
(Here is the director.)
(He can't bring himself to lift his head.)
(Moving forward with eyes cast down)
He can't look at us because he feels bad.
I couldn't look at them because I felt bad.
Director Back Koo Young.
Please deliver the result envelope.
Goodness.
There are three names there?
(Feeling nervous)
Who will be heading to the Last Stage?
(Please spare me.)
This is crazy.
I think it's going to be me.
The first worst choreographer...
This is torturing me.
I hope it's not one of us.
I feel like throwing up.
(The first worst choreographer)
is Renan.
(Renan)
(Last Stage: 24H's 3 Choreographers: Renan)
My mind just went blank at that moment.
As for Renan,
you have to give her a few directions on site...
for there to be changes.
(During Renan's center part shooting)
(I think Renan is off beat now.)
She kept going off beat.
Renan's are the ones that...
I remember the least from the video.
She lacked confidence in the group choreography.
I wish her facial expressions had been more visible.
I think it's more about who embodies...
and understood the energy that's meant for this video...
the most and the least.
You know, and finding the..
It's solely just that in this moment.
I kept thinking, "No way."
I'll hate them forever.
The Fight Judges had high praise...
for each choreographer's strengths and stage presence...
showcased in the film.
NaiN was the one who stood out to me.
When she took center,
the choreography looked very clean and precise.
There was something about it that drew me in.
I think INGYOO has a strong presence...
no matter what scene he's in.
Your screen presence has so much to do...
with the way you do choreography.
(Nodding)
- That's right. - Simeez, who was in the heels.
Yes.
I was really drawn...
to the person wearing heels.
This is her moment, her section, her part.
BADA has incredible impact as well.
You can always count on BADA.
I think she's incredibly good at expressing herself.
The fact that you can instantly tell,
"That's BADA," the moment her scene comes on...
is impessive because it's not something easy to do.
Another key part of the evaluation...
was how well you proved your presence.
Some choreographers also received criticism...
for areas that fell short.
(Sighing)
As for choreographer JEONG MIN JUN,
they commented that although he's an exceptional dancer,
his energy and presence in expressing himself...
through the film...
felt somewhat lacking.
I couldn't really understand it.
As for choreographer Kasper,
they commented that despite making major contributions in the process,
his presence didn't come across strongly enough...
in the final film.
I was never in the center...
doing movements that really expressed who I am.
I was only in the center for a brief bridge section.
As for choreographer BABYZOO,
they commented that, in the early draft stage,
nerves kept him from fully showcasing...
the strengths he had prepared.
Since I was the worst director candidate,
I thought it couldn't be helped.
Finally, as for choreographer Hash,
they commented that there were some memorable moments,
but it was a shame that she didn't make the most...
of the opportunity to show more of her own style.
I had a high chance to become the worst director candidate.
I felt hopeless.
(The 4 leading candidates for worst choreographer)
Now, one more choreographer...
will be heading to the Last Stage.
(Feeling uneasy)
(Sighing)
The second worst choreographer...
to head to the Last Stage: 24H...
I didn't have a director's cut as well.
That's why I was really nervous.
I was really scared. My head hurt so much.
The worst?
This might sound arrogant, but I'm not worried.
Please!
(Screaming)
The second worst choreographer...
is JEONG MIN JUN.
(JEONG MIN JUN is the second worst choreographer.)
What?
- What? - I never expected...
to hear MIN JUN's name. I was shocked.
We're in trouble. That was unexpected.
(JEONG MIN JUN will be heading to the Last Stage: 24H.)
(Looking down)
I really didn't see that coming.
I got the director's cut,
and I thought I did what Koo Young told me to do.
I don't understand why I have to go to the Last Stage.
He has the best energy when it comes to dancing.
But the energy of expressing himself in the film...
MIN JUN is lacking in that.
I've seen MIN JUN, I feel like he had moments too,
but again, not memorable.
So far, choreographers Renan and JEONG MIN JUN...
have been confirmed to go to the Last Stage.
Now, we only have to announce the last worst choreographer.
Goodness.
BABYZOO, Kasper, and Hash.
Who, among these three,
will be the last choreographer to head to the Last Stage?
It wouldn't be BABYZOO.
He did well in the chorus.
He did the choreography for the chorus.
I think it had a big impact.
Putting BABYZOO in the center...
was a brilliant move.
He's a really good performer.
- Yes. - BABYZOO.
Kasper supported Koo Young a lot.
(Whenever Director Back Koo Young asked for help, )
(Kasper immediately ran out.)
(He also assisted the camera director.)
(He took care of the other choreographers as well.)
(He even organized the formation for Back Koo Young.)
Kasper helped me a lot...
when I was directing on site.
I had a feeling it wouldn't be him.
Hash's part was brief, but her kick...
and the collar-grabbing scene were powerful.
I think she's pretty safe.
I'll announce the last person...
to head to the Last Stage.
I couldn't even put my name down as a choreographer.
I'm just Dancer One right now.
I feel so nervous.
I can't be heading to the Last Stage already.
I still have so much to show everyone.
I was really nervous. I didn't know what was going to happen.
The last worst choreographer...
to head to the Last Stage: 24H...
(is X.)
(She's shocked.)
(The third choreographer to head to the Last Stage...)
(will be revealed September 12 at noon.)
(The time limit for the Last Stage...)
(is just 24 hours.)
(That's crazy.)
(I had a feeling I wouldn't go there.)
(It feels ridiculous...)
(that I'm actually going to the Last Stage.)
(Let's show them what I've got and leave.)
(The choreographers find a table with many chairs.)
(Exclaiming)
(They prepared something unbelievable.)
(Do I have to use this the way it is?)
(How can I use these props in a creative way?)
(I'm going to flip this.)
(I want to flip it, but I can't.)
It's 300kg.
(I've never used props that much before.)
(I'm not good with props.)
(I shouldn't just take the risk.)
(I'll have to eliminate it.)
(Maybe I should use fewer props...)
(and focus more on the composition.)
(I'm good at making use of the composition.)
(I thought I'd be able to show what I'm good at.)
(I really have to go all out.)
(I'll make them regret picking me as the worst choreographer.)
(Renan vs. JEONG MIN JUN vs. X)
(The first Last Stage to determine the first elimination.)
(The person will be leaving...)
(this stage.)
(One team from here?)
(It's the first person to be eliminated.)
(It's fun. It's already fun! This is trouble!)
(Honey J!)
(You're amazing!)
(It's Sean Lew!)
Goodness!
(Goodness)
(Kyoka)
(She's crazy.)
(Make some noise)
(An impressive lineup of judges)
(How did they bring them here?)
(He's startled.)
(What's going on?)
(He made a boat?)
(He's a genius.)
(That's crazy.)
(Exclaiming)
(Amazing)
(Can this be beaten?)
(MIN JUN's performance...)
(didn't have as much of a dancing aspect...)
(as we had expected.)
(I wouldn't say this if he had crushed it with the dancing.)
I love it.
(That's so good!)
(They're all in shock.)
(Renan crushed it!)
(We're in trouble. Renan...)
(She's determined.)
(It really feels...)
(like I've watched a scene in a movie.)
(You did that in 24 hours.)
(That was spot on.)
(In just one day?)
(That's unbelievable.)
(It also captured a lot of the desperation...)
(you'd expect from a final stage.)
(Thank you so much...)
(for showing us a great performance.)
(I won't be eliminated.)
(Never.)
(I don't want to be eliminated.)
(I have to survive.)
(I think it's much better...)
(than MIN JUN's and X's.)
(I love it.)
(Why is it always me?)
(Is this really happening?)
(Am I...)
(The Last Stage...)
(There's only a 30 percent chance of surviving that.)
(I'll just go home.)
(There's nothing I can do with this.)
(TVING's Last Stage: 24H, the last directing performances...)
(of the 3 choreographers will unfold.)